KGI	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(A	O
licenced	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
as	O
defined	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O

ICBCI	B-J
(Joint	O
Lead	O
Manager	O
only)	O

Livermore	B-ORG
Holdings	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
Unit	O
1214A,	O
12/F,	O
Tower	O
II	O
Cheung	O
Sha	O
Wan	O
Plaza	O
833	O
Road	O
Kowloon,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Jian	I-PERSON
Xigao	E-PERSON
(蹇錫高)	O
Room	O
106,	O
2	O
Yi'erjiu	O
Street	O
Xigang	O
District	O
Dalian,	O
Liaoning	O
PRC	O

CLSA	S-J

Joint	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinators	E-TITLE
UBS	B-ORG
AG	I-ORG
Hong	I-ORG
Kong	I-ORG
Branch	E-ORG

Authorized	B-TITLE
representatives	E-TITLE
.	O
Mr.	B-PERSON
Qi	I-PERSON
Mingzhi	E-PERSON
(齊明智)	O
1001,	O
Block	O
A	O
Baocui	O
Garden	O
No.	O
2045	O
Golden	O
Paddy	O
Road	O
Luohu	O
District	O
Shenzhen	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Yunyan	B-PERSON
Hu	E-PERSON
(胡雲雁)	O
102,	O
1/F-3/F,	O
No.	O
225,	O
Xinhai	O
Nanli	O
Majuqiao	O
Tongzhou	O
District	O
Beijing,	O
PRC	O

Auditors	B-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Reporting	I-TITLE
Accountants	E-TITLE
Mazars	B-ORG
CPA	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Guantao	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Firm	E-ORG
18/F,	O
Tower	O
B,	O
Xinsheng	O
Plaza	O
5	O
Finance	O
Street,	O
Xicheng	O
District	O
Beijing	O
China	O

Authorised	B-TITLE
representative	E-TITLE
(for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
Companies	O
Ordinance)	O

David	B-PERSON
Lai	I-PERSON
&	I-PERSON
Tan	E-PERSON

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ding	I-PERSON
Weisong	E-PERSON
(丁唯淞)	O
1801,	O
18/F,	O
World-wide	O
House	O
19	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Imran	B-ORG
Muntaz	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co.	E-ORG
Office	O
8	O
Building,	O
35th	O
Floor	O
Zone	O
G	O
Sudirman	O
Central	O
Business	O
District	O
(SCBD)	O
Lot.	O
28	O
J1,	O
Jend,	O
Kav.	O
52-53	O
Jakarta	O
12190	O
Republic	O
of	O
Indonesia	O
as	O
to	O
international	O
sanctions	O
law:	O

Si	B-PERSON
Xiaobing	E-PERSON
(司小兵)	O
No.	O
29,	O
Youyi	O
North	O
Road,	O
Hexi	O
District,	O
Tianjin,	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Cheung	I-PERSON
Yuk	I-PERSON
Chuen	E-PERSON
(張玉存)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
KAN	I-PERSON
Chung	I-PERSON
Nin,	I-PERSON
Tony	E-PERSON
(簡松年)	O
House	O
No.	O
9	O
Monte	O
Villa,	O
6	O
Path	O
Kau	O
To	O
Shan	O
Shatin	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Fortune	B-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
43/F,	O
COSCO	O
Tower	O
183	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Manager	E-TITLE
Head	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Shoulders	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
conduct	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O

TUS	B-ORG
Corporate	I-ORG
Finance	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Freeman	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
engage	O
in	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
securities)	O
and	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
regulated	O
activities	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
LEUNG	I-PERSON
Suet	I-PERSON
Lun	E-PERSON

Dr.	B-PERSON
Zhang	I-PERSON
Xiangwei	E-PERSON
(張湘偉)	O
.	O
Room	O
2901,	O
Courtyard	O
2	O
No.	O
72	O
Nonglin	O
Down	O
Road	O
Dongshan	O
District	O
Guangzhou	O
City	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Maxa	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
1908,	O
Harbour	O
Center	O
25	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
as	O
defined	O
SFO)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
CHUNG	I-PERSON
Chong	I-PERSON
Sun	E-PERSON
(鍾創新)	O
G/F,	O
Block	O
1,	O
iLife	O
222	O
Shek	O
Wu	O
Tong	O
Pat	O
Heung,	O
Yuen	O
Long	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Maxa	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Flat	O
08,	O
19/F	O
Harbour	O
Centre	O
25	O
Road	O
Wanchai,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Reporting	B-TITLE
Accountants	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Auditor	E-TITLE
KPMG	B-ORG

Crosby	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
5/F,	O
Capital	O
Centre	O
151	O
Gloucester	O
Road	O
Wanchai,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	E-TITLE
Haitong	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O
for	O
purpose	O
of	O
SFO)	O

Plutus	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Luis	B-ORG
BARRETO	E-ORG
53	O
Crooked	O
Stick	O
Road	O
Concord	O
Ontario,	O
L4K	O
1P4	O
Canada	O

91	O
Auditor	B-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
reporting	I-TITLE
accountant	E-TITLE
PricewaterhouseCoopers	B-ORG

Wellink	B-ORG
CPA	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Rooms	O
803	O
–	O
4	O
Kin	O
Wing	O
Commercial	O
Building	O
24	O
30	O
Street	O
Tuen	O
Mun	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Dongyue	I-PERSON
Cheng	E-PERSON
(程東躍)	O
(Chairman)	O

Company	O
Secretary	O
Mr.	O
Wong	O
Shing	O
Mun	O
(FCCA,	O
HKICPA)	O

China	B-ORG
Merchants	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Co.,	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Auditors	B-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
reporting	I-TITLE
accountants	E-TITLE
KPMG	B-ORG

Tax	I-ORG
advisers	E-TITLE
Baker	B-ORG
Tilly	I-ORG
Monteiro	I-ORG
Heng	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Sdn.	I-ORG
Bhd.	E-ORG

DBS	O
Bank	O
Tower,	O
17th	O
Floor	O
Suite	O
1701,	O
Jl.	O
Prof.	O
Dr.	O
Satrio	O
Kav	O
3-5	O
Jakarta	O
12940	O
Indonesia	O
as	O
to	O
Singaporean	O
law:	O

SPDB	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
a	O
licenced	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
SFO	O

First	B-ORG
Fidelity	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
(International)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
securities)	O
and	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
Unit	O
1405,	O
Allied	O
Kajima	O
Building	O
138	O
Gloucester	O
Road	O
Wanchai,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
I	O
Win	O
Securities	O
activity	O
Room	O
1916,	O
Plaza	O
188	O
Connaught	O
West	O
Sai	O
Wan,	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Yee	I-PERSON
Man	I-PERSON
WONG	E-PERSON

Mr.	B-PERSON
Woo	I-PERSON
Yuen	I-PERSON
Ping	E-PERSON
Flat	O
F,	O
9th	O
Floor	O
Block	O
M2,	O
Yoho	O
Midtown	O
9	O
Lung	O
Street	O
Long,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Dong	I-PERSON
Hui	E-PERSON
(董暉)	O
Flat	O
2-15H,	O
Block	O
3	O
Phase	O
6	O
Xinghaimingcheng	O
Nanshan	O
District	O
Shenzhen	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
(廣東省深圳市南山區星海名城六期3棟	O
2-15H)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Sy	I-PERSON
Man	E-PERSON
Chiu(許文超)	O
Flat	O
B,	O
15/F.,	O
Block	O
1	O
Cascades	O
93	O
Chung	O
Hau	O
Street	O
Ho	O
Tin	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Lijun	B-PERSON
Xin	E-PERSON
(辛利軍)	O
No.	O
206,	O
Unit	O
4,	O
Building	O
3	O
Fengniaojiayuan	O
Beijing	O
People's	O
Republic	O
of	O
China	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Leung	I-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Che	I-PERSON
Ming	I-PERSON
Miranda	E-PERSON
(梁陳智明女士)	O
18/F,	O
Flat	O
B	O
Rome	O
Court	O
Realty	O
Gardens	O
41	O
Conduit	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mrs.	B-PERSON
SU	I-PERSON
TAN	I-PERSON
Jennifer	I-PERSON
Sze	I-PERSON
Tink	E-PERSON
(蘇陳詩婷女士)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
10/F	O
Carnation	O
Court	O
43	O
Tai	O
Hang	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wan	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON
Hei	E-PERSON
31/F.,	O
148	O
Electric	O
Road	O
North	O
Point	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
3	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lim	I-PERSON
Wee	I-PERSON
Pin	E-PERSON
(林偉彬)	O
Block	O
203C	O
Compassvale	O
Road	O
#04-31	O
Singapore	O
543203	O
Singaporean	O

Legal	B-TITLE
advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sponsor,	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Manager,	I-TITLE
Bookrunner	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriter	E-TITLE

Joint	B-TITLE
company	I-TITLE
secretaries	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Leng	I-PERSON
Xuejun	I-PERSON
Lei	I-PERSON
Kin	I-PERSON
Keong	E-PERSON
ACIS,	O
ACS,	O
HKICPA	O

Citigroup	B-ORG
Global	I-ORG
Markets	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(Joint	O
Bookrunner	O
and	O
Joint	O
Lead	O
Manager	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Public	O
Offering	O
only)	O
50th	O
Floor,	O
Champion	O
Tower	O
3	O
Garden	O
Road,	O
Central	O

ChaoShang	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
a	O
licenced	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
2	O
future	O
contracts)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
SFO	O

Ng	B-PERSON
Kong	I-PERSON
Hock	E-PERSON
(黃康福)	O
House	O
6B,	O
Hougang	O
Street	O
11	O
#15-18	O
The	O
Minton	O
Singapore	O
534083	O
Man	O
Yun	O
Wah	O
(文潤華)	O
Unit	O
912,	O
9/F,	O
Two	O
Harbourfront	O
22	O
Tak	O
Fung	O
Hunghom	O
Kowloon,	O
Hong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
LEE	I-PERSON
Yau	I-PERSON
Ching	E-PERSON
(李友情)	O
.	O
Flat	O
B,	O
7th	O
Floor,	O
Tower	O
2	O
The	O
Austin	O
8	O
Wui	O
Cheung	O
Road	O
Tsim	O
Sha	O
Tsui	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Li	I-PERSON
Ching	I-PERSON
Yi	E-PERSON
(	O
ACIS,	O
ACS	O
)	O
14th	O
Floor,	O
Golden	O
Centre	O
188	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Wong	B-PERSON
Jovi	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON
Wing	E-PERSON
(王志榮)	O
Flat	O
D,	O
13/F	O
Block	O
1,	O
University	O
Heights	O
No.	O
23	O
Pokfield	O
Road	O
Kennedy	O
Town	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Manager	E-TITLE
CNCB	B-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

CMB	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
45F,	O
Champion	O
Tower	O
3	O
Garden	O
Road	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
WU	I-PERSON
Tai	I-PERSON
Cheung	E-PERSON
(胡大祥)	O
(Chairman)	O

As	O
to	O
PRC	O
law:	O
Jingtian	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Gongcheng	E-ORG
Attorneys	O
At	O
Law	O
Suite	O
45,	O
K.	O
Wah	O
Centre	O
1010	O
Huaihai	O
Road	O
(M)	O
Xuhui	O
District	O
Shanghai	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wu	I-PERSON
Yong	E-PERSON
(吳勇)	O
Room	O
601,	O
Building	O
No.	O
2,	O
5,	O
Ren	O
Yuan,	O
Jianye	O
District,	O
Nanjing	O
City,	O
Jiangsu	O
Province,	O
the	O
PRC	O

Allbright	O
Law	O
Offices	O
9,	O
11,	O
12/F	O
Shanghai	O
Tower	O
501	O
Yincheng	O
Middle	O
Road	O
Pudong	O
New	O
District	O
the	O
PRC	O

Internal	B-TITLE
control	I-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE
Billy	B-ORG
Ho	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Associates	I-ORG
CPA	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Ms.	B-PERSON
Caroline	I-PERSON
Irene	I-PERSON
Chen	E-PERSON
Unit	O
No.	O
4124,	O
Block	O
4	O
Lido	O
Courts,	O
Place	O
6,	O
Jiangtai	O
Road	O
Beijing	O
PRC	O

Authorised	B-TITLE
representatives	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Jiang	I-PERSON
Xiaohuang	E-PERSON
(蔣孝黃)	O
Room	O
0804,	O
Building	O
No.	O
04	O
Jincheng	O
Zhixing	O
58	O
Qihong	O
Road	O
Suzhou	O
Industrial	O
Park,	O
Jiangsu	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Liu	I-PERSON
Teng	E-PERSON
(劉騰)	O
Flat	O
E,	O
25/F,	O
Choi	O
Tien	O
Mans	O
Horizon	O
Gardens	O
11	O
Tai	O
Koo	O
Wan	O
Road	O
Taikoo	O
Shing	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Dato'	B-PERSON
Ng	I-PERSON
Kwang	I-PERSON
Hua	E-PERSON
.	O
No.	O
9,	O
Jalan	O
Bukit	O
Mewah	O
9/10B	O
Taman	O
Fasa	O
10	O
43000	O
Kajang	O
Selangor,	O
Malaysia	O

VDB	B-ORG
Loi	I-ORG
Co.,	I-ORG
Ltd.	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Leng	I-PERSON
Wai	E-PERSON
(Chairman)	O

PARTIES	B-SKIP
INVOLVED	I-SKIP
IN	I-SKIP
GLOBAL	I-SKIP
OFFERING:	E-SKIP

Haiwen	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Partners	E-ORG

Authorised	B-TITLE
representatives	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Tsui	I-PERSON
Kai	E-PERSON
Kwong(徐繼光)	O
No.37,	O
4th	O
Street	O
Section	O
C	O
Fairview	O
Park	O
Yuen	O
Long	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Kwong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
REN	I-PERSON
Wei	E-PERSON
.	O
No.	O
5B	O
Building	O
no.	O
509	O
Daxiyang	O
Xincheng	O
33	O
Guangshun	O
North	O
Street	O
Chaoyang	O
District,	O
Beijing	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wong	I-PERSON
Kin	I-PERSON
Pong	I-PERSON
Edmond	E-PERSON
(HKICPA,	O
FCCA)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Min	I-PERSON
Frank	I-PERSON
Zeng	E-PERSON
(曾敏)	O
17	O
Needle	O
Grass	O
Irvine	O
California	O
92603	O
U.S.	O

Reporting	B-TITLE
Accountants	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Independent	I-TITLE
Auditor	E-TITLE

Authorised	B-TITLE
representatives	E-TITLE
(for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
Listing	O
Rules)	O
Mr.	B-PERSON
CHU	I-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
Fun	E-PERSON
(朱國歡先生)	O
Flat	O
B,	O
2nd	O
Floor	O
Peak	O
Garden	O
Court	O
11	O
Magnolia	O
Road	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

34th	O
Floor,	O
Tower	O
3	O
China	O
Central	O
Place	O
77	O
Jianguo	O
Road	O
Beijing	O
100025	O
PRC	O
(PRC	O
attorneys-at-law)	O

Company	O
Secretary	O
Ms.	O
Suet	O
Wing	O
Leung	O
(	O
梁雪穎	O
)	O
(ACIS,	O
ACS)	O

Maxa	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
1908,	O
Harbour	O
Centre	O
25	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
I	B-ORG
Win	I-ORG
Securities	E-ORG
Room	O
1916	O
Plaza	O
188	O
Connaught	O
West	O

Co-Manager	S-TITLE
Yuzhou	B-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Holdings	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
and	O
permitted	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
Securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
Securities)	O
9	O
(asset	O
Management)	O
of	O
regulated	O
activities	O
as	O
defined	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Zhang	I-PERSON
Yitao	E-PERSON
(張藝濤)	O
Room	O
301,	O
No.	O
13	O
Building	O
Minghuyuan	O
Dongfangtaiyangcheng	O
Renhe	O
Town	O
Shunyi	O
District	O
Beijing	O
PRC	O

Co-Manager	S-TITLE
Zundiao	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
Room	O
601,	O
6/F	O
On	O
Hong	O
Commercial	O
Building	O
145	O
Hennessy	O
Road,	O
Wanchai	O
Kong	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinator	E-TITLE
---------------	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
CHAN	I-PERSON
Tak	I-PERSON
Yiu	E-PERSON
(陳德耀)	O
House	O
32B,	O
1/F	O
JC	O
Castle	O
18	O
Shan	O
Tong	O
Road	O
Tai	O
Po	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Zhongtai	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
as	O
defined	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O
19th	O
Floor	O
Li	O
Po	O
Chun	O
Chambers	O
189	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	E-TITLE
CMBC	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
45/F,	O
One	O
Exchange	O
Square	O
8	O
Connaught	O
Place	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Grand	B-ORG
Moore	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
and	O
permitted	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O

Receiving	B-TITLE
bank(s)	E-TITLE
Hang	B-ORG
Seng	I-ORG
Bank	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Kwok	B-PERSON
Yih	I-PERSON
&	I-PERSON
Chan	E-PERSON
Suites	O
2103-05	O
21st	O
Floor,	O
9	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Yuanta	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
by	O
the	O
SFC	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
2	O
futures	O
contracts),	O
4	O
(advising	O
5	O
6	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
and	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
SFO	O

AllBright	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Offices	I-ORG
Hangzhou	I-ORG
Office	E-ORG

Floor,	O
Nanyang	O
Plaza	O
57	O
Hung	O
To	O
Road	O
Kwun	O
Tong,	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Audit	B-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
MA	I-PERSON
Andrew	I-PERSON
Chiu	I-PERSON
Cheung	E-PERSON
(Chairman)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wu	I-PERSON
Man	I-PERSON
Sun	E-PERSON
(Certified	O
Public	O
Accountant)	O
Room	O
2705-6,	O
27/F	O
Tower	O
One,	O
Lippo	O
Centre	O
89	O
Queensway	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Alpha	B-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Group	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(Dealing	O
in	O
Securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
as	O
defined	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O
Room	O
A,	O
17/F,	O
Fortune	O
House	O
61	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Legal	B-TITLE
Advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
laws:	O
Sidley	B-ORG
Austin	E-ORG
39/F	O
Two	O
Int'l	O
Finance	O
Centre	O
Central	O

Auditor	B-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Reporting	I-TITLE
Accountants	E-TITLE
Deloitte	B-ORG
Touche	I-ORG
Tohmatsu	E-ORG
Certified	O
Public	O
35/F,	O
One	O
Pacific	O
Place	O
88	O
Queensway	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Ruibang	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
9/F	O
Sang	O
Woo	O
Building,	O
227-228	O
Gloucester	O
Road,	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
Qian	I-PERSON
Weizhu	E-PERSON
(錢衛珠)	O
Room	O
1202,	O
No.14,	O
Lane	O
300,	O
Jinxiu	O
Road,	O
Pudong	O
New	O
District,	O
Shanghai,	O
PRC	O

Forthright	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Yang	I-PERSON
Dengfeng	E-PERSON
(楊登峰)	O
Flat	O
10A,	O
Block	O
3	O
Shekou	O
Gaoshan	O
Huayuan	O
Industrial	O
Eighth	O
Road	O
Nanshan	O
District	O
Shenzhen	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
(廣東省深圳市南山區工業八路蛇口高山	O
花園3棟10A房)	O

Non-executive	B-TITLE
Directors	E-TITLE

Mr.	B-PERSON
Tong	I-PERSON
Yee	I-PERSON
Ming	E-PERSON
(湯以銘先生)	O
Flat	O
B,	O
6/F,	O
Block	O
11	O
Double	O
Cove	O
Summit	O
Ma	O
On	O
Shan	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Mao	I-PERSON
Chaosheng	E-PERSON
(毛超聖)	O
Room	O
908	O
Building	O
2	O
Xuefu	O
Mingdu	O
No.	O
268	O
Wangjiang	O
West	O
Road	O
Shushan	O
District	O
Hefei	O
City	O
Anhui	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Ko	I-PERSON
Sau	I-PERSON
Mee	E-PERSON
(高秀媚女士)	O
57/F,	O
Block	O
27,	O
Celestial	O
Heights	O
80	O
Sheung	O
Shing	O
Street	O
Ho	O
Man	O
Tin,	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Gram	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
1209,	O
12th	O
Floor	O
Nan	O
Fung	O
Tower	O
88	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central/	O
173	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
Che	I-PERSON
Chung	E-PERSON
(郭芝聰)	O
Room	O
4,	O
13/F	O
Mai	O
Hing	O
House	O
No.	O
3-4	O
Hon	O
Road	O
Pokfulam,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Co-Lead	B-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Sinomax	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
CLSA	B-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Reporting	B-TITLE
accountants	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
auditors	E-TITLE
Mazars	B-ORG
CPA	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Certified	O
Public	O
Accountants	O
42nd	O
Floor,	O
Central	O
Plaza	O
18	O
Harbour	O
Road	O
Wanchai,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
China	B-ORG
Industrial	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
a	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
by	O
the	O
SFC	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
SFO	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
LI	I-PERSON
Xin	E-PERSON
(李欣先生)	O
YU	I-PERSON
Linkang	E-PERSON
(喻霖康先生)	O

Legal	B-TITLE
advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor,	I-TITLE
Joint	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	E-TITLE

Clifford	B-ORG
Chance	E-ORG

Ms.	B-PERSON
Suet	I-PERSON
Wing	I-PERSON
Leung	E-PERSON
(	O
梁雪穎	O
)	O

Independent	B-TITLE
Property	I-TITLE
Valuer	E-TITLE
Laurelcap	B-ORG
Sdn.	I-ORG
Bhd.	E-ORG
Suite	O
E-6-2	O
&	O
E-7-2	O
East	O
Wing,	O
Subang	O
Square	O
Jalan	O
SS1514G	O
47500	O
Jaya	O
Selangor	O
Malaysia	O

Audit	B-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Fan	I-PERSON
Chun	I-PERSON
Wah,	I-PERSON
Andrew	E-PERSON
(范駿華先生),	O
J.P.	O
(Chairman)	O
Lu	O
Qingxing	O
(呂慶星先生)	O
Yan	O
Aru	O
(閆阿儒先生)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
TANG	I-PERSON
Sher	I-PERSON
Kin	E-PERSON
(鄧社堅)	O
Flat	O
C,	O
27/F	O
Tower	O
1	O
The	O
Beaumount	O
II	O
6	O
Shek	O
Kok	O
Road	O
Tseung	O
Kwan	O
O	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Legal	B-TITLE
advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Company	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law	O
Deacons	S-ORG
5th	O
Floor	O
Alexandra	O
House	O
18	O
Chater	O
Road	O
Central	O

The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	B-PERSON
Hugo	I-PERSON
George	I-PERSON
William	E-PERSON
Swire,	O
KCMG,	O
MP	O
Swire	O

Bagus	B-ORG
Enrico	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Partners	E-ORG

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Southwest	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Brokerage	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
by	O
the	O
SFC	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
SFO	O
40/F.,	O
Lee	O
Garden	O
One	O
33	O
Hysan	O
Avenue	O
Causeway	O
Bay	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Lego	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
301,	O
3/F,	O
China	O
Building	O
29	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
engaged	O
in	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Registered	O
Office	O
.	O
c/o	O
Harneys	B-ORG
Fiduciary	I-ORG
(Cayman)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
4th	O
Floor,	O
Harbour	O
Place	O
103	O
South	O
Church	O
Street	O
George	O
Town	O
P.O.	O
Box	O
10240	O
Grand	O
Cayman	O
KY1-1002	O
Islands	O

Head	O
office	O
and	O
principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Unit	O
1001–02,	O
10/F,	O
Delta	O
House	O
3	O
On	O
Yiu	O
Street	O
Shatin,	O
New	O
Territories	O

Crosby	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
6	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
and	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

WONG	B-PERSON
Hung	I-PERSON
Pan	E-PERSON
(黃鴻斌)	O
(FCPA,	O
ACIS,	O
ACS)	O

Board	O
Committees	O
Risk	O
Management	O
Committee	O

Audit	B-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Lai	I-PERSON
Yat	I-PERSON
Kwong	I-PERSON
Fred	E-PERSON
(Chairman)	O
Lui	I-PERSON
Ho	I-PERSON
Ming	I-PERSON
Paul	I-PERSON
Woo	I-PERSON
Chun	I-PERSON
Fai	I-PERSON

Internal	B-TITLE
control	I-TITLE
adviser	E-TITLE
HLB	B-ORG
Hodgson	I-ORG
Impey	I-ORG
Cheng	I-ORG
Risk	I-ORG
Advisory	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
31st	O
Floor,	O
Gloucester	O
Tower	O
The	O
Landmark	O
11	O
Pedder	O
Street	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Principal	O
Executive	O
Offices	O
of	O
Main	O
Operations	O
F4/F5,	O
Building	O
C,	O
Sunland	O
International	O
No.	O
999	O
Zhouhai	O
Road	O
Pudong	O
Shanghai	O
200137	O
China	O

Beijing	B-ORG
Dentons	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Offices,	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG
7/F,	O
Building	O
D,	O
Parkview	O
Green	O
FangCaoDi	O
No.	O
9	O
Dongdaqiao	O
Road	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
PRC	O
as	O
to	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
law:	O

RHTLaw	B-ORG
Taylor	I-ORG
Wessing	I-ORG
Vietnam	E-ORG

Audit	O
committee	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lim	O
Boon	O
Cheng	O
(林文正先生)	O
(Chairman)	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
Jingsong	I-PERSON
Wang	E-PERSON
Ms.	B-PERSON
Weiwei	I-PERSON
Chen	E-PERSON
Nomination	B-TITLE
committee	E-TITLE

Sorrento	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
11/F,	O
The	O
Wellington	O
198	O
Street	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Fu	I-PERSON
Xi	E-PERSON
(符熙)	O
Room	O
351-1-1701,	O
Wankehongjun	O
1	O
Daxueyuan	O
Road	O
Hongshan	O
District	O
Wuhan	O
PRC	O

Shanxi	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
A,	O
29/F,	O
Admiralty	O
Center	O
Tower	O
1	O
18	O
Harcourt	O
Road	O
Admiralty,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Property	I-ORG
valuer	E-TITLE
Jones	B-ORG
Lang	I-ORG
LaSalle	I-ORG
Consultants	I-ORG
Pte	I-ORG
Ltd	E-ORG
1	O
Paya	O
Lebar	O
Link	O
#10-08	O
Quarter	O
Tower	O
2	O
Singapore	O
408533	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Law	I-PERSON
Lap	I-PERSON
Tak	E-PERSON
(羅納德)	O
Flat	O
B,	O
6/F.,	O
Tower	O
4	O
Discovery	O
Park	O
398	O
Castle	O
Peak	O
Road	O
Tsuen	O
Wan	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Red	B-ORG
Sun	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
3303,	O
33/F	O
West	O
Tower,	O
Shun	O
Tak	O
Centre	O
168–200	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
engaged	O
in	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Morgan	B-ORG
Stanley	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
46/F,	O
International	O
Commerce	O
Centre	O
1	O
Austin	O
Road	O
West	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Aristo	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
and	O
headquarters	O
in	O
China	O
5D-506	O
F1.6	O
Block	O
Tianfa	O
Building	O
Tianan	O
Chegongmiao	O
Industrial	O
Park	O
Futian	O
District	O
Shenzhen,	O

Hu	B-PERSON
Yangyang	E-PERSON
(胡洋洋)	O
Room	O
503,	O
Building	O
21	O
23	O
Lanlin	O
Road	O
Pudong	O
New	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lui	I-PERSON
Wing	I-PERSON
Nam	E-PERSON
(呂永南)	O
Flat	O
E,	O
37/F.,	O
Block	O
7	O
Royal	O
Ascot	O
1	O
Tsun	O
King	O
Road	O
Fo	O
Tan,	O
N.	O
T.	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Block	O
18	O
Unit	O
302	O
Lane	O
388	O
Furong	O
Jiang	O
Road	O
Changning	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
China	O
Singaporean	O
Mr.	O
Gary	O
J.	O
Wojtaszek	O
Director	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinator	E-TITLE
Elstone	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
Suite	O
1601-04,	O
16/F.	O
West	O
Tower,	O
Shun	O
Tak	O
Centre	O
168-200	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Audit	O
committee	O
Mr.	O
Lim	O
Chee	O
Hoong	O
(Chairperson)	O
Heng	O
Choon	O
Ms.	O
Ng	O
Siok	O
Hui	O

Skadden,	B-ORG
Arps,	I-ORG
Slate,	I-ORG
Meagher	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Flom	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Fan	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON
Chiu	E-PERSON
(范智超)	O
Flat	O
A	O
8/F,	O
Ngar	O
Lan	O
Mans	O
–	O
Westlands	O
Court,	O
9	O
Road,	O
Quarry	O
Bay,	O
Hong	O
Kong,	O
China	O

As	O
to	O
U.S.	O
trade	O
law:	O
DLA	B-ORG
Piper	I-ORG
Singapore	I-ORG
Pte.	I-ORG
Ltd.	E-ORG
80	O
Raffles	O
Place	O
#48-01	O
UOB	O
Plaza	O
1	O
048624	O

As	O
to	O
PRC	O
law:	O
JunZeJun	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Offices	E-ORG
Attorneys-at-law,	O
28th	O
and	O
29th	O
Floor	O
Rongchao	O
Economic	O
Trade	O
Center	O
No.	O
4028	O
Jintian	O
Road	O
Futian	O
District	O
Shenzhen	O
518035	O

Dato'	B-PERSON
Tan	I-PERSON
MS	E-PERSON
No.	O
18,	O
Jalan	O
Ponderosa	O
1/9	O
Taman	O
81100	O
Johor	O
Bahru	O
Johor,	O
Malaysia	O

As	O
to	O
PRC	O
laws	O
(in	O
relation	O
the	O
Proceeding)	O
Hylands	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Firm	E-ORG
9/F,	O
Dinghe	O
Plaza	O
No.	O
100	O
Fuhua	O
3rd	O
Road	O
Futian	O
District	O
Shenzhen	O
China	O

9/F,	O
Connaught	O
Harbourfront	O
House	O
35-36	O
Road	O
West	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activities)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wei	I-PERSON
Wang	E-PERSON
(王瑋)	O
Room	O
1602	O
No.12	O
Alley	O
888	O
Changning	O
Road	O
District	O
Shanghai,	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Luo	I-PERSON
Qiang	E-PERSON
(羅強先生)	O
No.	O
5,	O
Unit	O
2,	O
Dong	O
21	O
No.123	O
Shunyuanhuan	O
Street	O
Gaoxin	O
District,	O
Chengdu	O
PRC	O

China	B-ORG
Everbright	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
12/F,	O
Centre	O
108	O
Gloucester	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Authorised	O
Representatives	O
Ms.	O
Qiao	O
Haixia	O
(喬海俠)	O
Room	O
402,	O
No.651	O
Hexiang	O
West	O
Road	O
Siming	O
District	O
Xiamen,	O
Fujian	O
Province,	O
PRC	O

As	O
to	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
law	O
Conyers	B-ORG
Dill	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Pearman	E-ORG
Cricket	O
Square	O
Hutchins	O
Drive	O
P.O.	O
Box	O
2681	O
Grand	O
Cayman,	O
KY1-1111	O

Authorised	B-TITLE
representatives	E-TITLE
(for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
GEM	O
Listing	O
Rules	O
or	O
Companies	O
Ordinance)	O

Squire	B-ORG
Patton	I-ORG
Boggs	I-ORG
(US)	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG
275	O
Battery	O
Street	O
Suite	O
2600	O
San	O
Francisco	O
California	O
94111	O
United	O
States	O

Audit	B-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Cheong	I-PERSON
Tat	E-PERSON
(陳昌達)	O
(chairman)	O
Cheung	I-PERSON
Wai	I-PERSON
Hung	E-PERSON
(張偉雄)	O
Ms.	B-PERSON
Chen	I-PERSON
Weijie	E-PERSON
(陳維洁)	O

LIN	B-PERSON
Lin	E-PERSON
(林林)	O
Room	O
2102,	O
No.168	O
Lane	O
No.1038,	O
Huashan	O
Road	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Morgan	B-ORG
Stanley	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Public	O
Offering	O
only)	O
46/F,	O
International	O
Commerce	O
Centre	O
1	O
Austin	O
Road	O
West	O
Kowloon	O

As	O
to	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
law:	O
Conyers	B-ORG
Dill	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Pearman	E-ORG
Cricket	O
Square	O
Hutchins	O
Drive	O
P.O.	O
Box	O
2681	O
Grand	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Leung	I-PERSON
Shui	I-PERSON
Bing	E-PERSON
(ACIS;	O
ACS)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lin	I-PERSON
Weiguo	E-PERSON
(林偉國)	O
No.16	O
Changzhi	O
Road,	O
Huli	O
District	O
Xiamen,	O
Fujian	O
Province,	O
PRC	O
Chinese	O

As	O
to	O
Canada	O
law:	O
Gowling	B-ORG
WLG	I-ORG
(Canada)	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG
50	O
Queen	O
Street	O
North,	O
Suite	O
1020	O
PO	O
Box	O
2248,	O
Kitchener	O
Ontario	O
N2H	O
6M2	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Shuk	I-PERSON
Fong	E-PERSON
Mr.	B-PERSON
Mak	B-PERSON
Ping	I-PERSON
Leung	E-PERSON
(alias:	O
Wah	E-PERSON
Cheung)	O
Dr.	B-PERSON
Sat	I-PERSON
Chui	I-PERSON
Wan	I-PERSON
Wong	I-PERSON
Shiu	I-PERSON
Hoi	I-PERSON
Peter	E-PERSON

Mr.	B-PERSON
XU	I-PERSON
Chungang	E-PERSON
(徐純剛)	O
Room	O
502	O
Building	O
5	O
Jinshui	O
Jiayuan	O
No.	O
7268	O
Yatai	O
Street	O
Nanguan	O
District	O
Changchun	O
City	O
Jilin	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lui,	I-PERSON
Wing	I-PERSON
Yat	I-PERSON
Christopher	E-PERSON
(呂穎一先生)	O
Level	O
54,	O
Hopewell	O
Centre	O
183	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
East	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Mai	I-PERSON
Boliang	E-PERSON
(麥伯良)	O
Room	O
32C	O
Tian	O
Hai	O
Hao	O
Jing	O
Yuan	O
No.	O
44	O
Ai	O
Rong	O
Road	O
Nanshan	O
District	O
Shenzhen	O
Guangdong	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Chun	I-PERSON
Hung,	I-PERSON
Vincent	E-PERSON
(陳鎮洪)	O
Flat	O
2401	O
24th	O
Floor,	O
Block	O
A	O
Villa	O
Lotto,	O
18	O
Broadwood	O
Road	O
Happy	O
Valley	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

CRIC	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
2007	O
&	O
2403,	O
Great	O
Eagle	O
Centre	O
23	O
Harbour	O
Road,	O
Wan	O
Chai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Lee	I-PERSON
Ming	I-PERSON
Chu	I-PERSON
Jade	E-PERSON
(李明珠)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
3/F	O
Yick	O
Fai	O
Building	O
20	O
Sai	O
Ching	O
Street	O
Yuen	O
Long	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

CRIC	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
and	O
permitted	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
securities)	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
of	O
regulated	O
activity	O

Audit	O
committee	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fan,	O
Chiu	O
Tat	O
Martin	O
(范招達)	O
(Chairman)	O

VMS	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
49/F,	O
One	O
Exchange	O
Square	O
8	O
Connaught	O
Place	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Zhou	B-PERSON
Li(周禮)	O
Room	O
15A,	O
Building	O
5	O
Xindeya	O
Apartment	O
Hangzhou	O
City	O
Zhejiang	O
Province	O
PRC	O
Li	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Tian	I-PERSON
Ye	E-PERSON
(田野)	O
----------	O
16fl,	O
Unit	O
3,	O
Building	O
7	O
No.	O
966	O
Tianfu	O
2nd	O
Street	O
Chengdu,	O
Sichuan	O
Province,	O
PRC	O
(中國四川省成都市天府二街966號7棟3	O
單元16層)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Zhang	I-PERSON
Yingwei	E-PERSON
(張英偉)	O
Room	O
2405,	O
Floor	O
24,	O
Building	O
1	O
Court	O
2,	O
Li	O
Ze	O
Road	O
Fengtai	O
District	O
Beijing,	O
PRC	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
GUO	I-PERSON
Jie	E-PERSON
(郭杰)	O
No.	O
706,	O
Unit	O
5	O
Block	O
District	O
3,	O
Yuanda	O
Park	O
Century	O
City	O
Haidian	O
Beijing,	O
PRC	O

Compliance	B-TITLE
Advisor	E-TITLE
Octal	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

ABCI	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
a	O
licenced	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
SFO	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
LI	I-PERSON
Luqiang	E-PERSON
(李璐強先生)	O
Room	O
306,	O
Building	O
No.3	O
Sheng	O
Shi	O
Jia	O
Yuan	O
Court	O
No.	O
98,	O
Jianguo	O
Road	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
Beijing,	O
PRC	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Lin	I-PERSON
Zichan	E-PERSON
(林姿嬋)	O
Room	O
502,	O
Building	O
10	O
No.	O
27	O
Xinjian	O
Community	O
Lingxi	O
Town	O
Cangnan	O
County	O
Zhejiang	O
Province	O
PRC	O

As	O
to	O
PRC	O
law:	O
Jingtian	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Gongcheng	E-ORG
34/F,	O
Tower	O
3,	O
China	O
Central	O
Place	O
77	O
Jianguo	O
Road,	O
Beijing	O
100025,	O

Risk	B-TITLE
Control	I-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
.	O
Mr.	B-PERSON
CHEN	I-PERSON
Jianmin	E-PERSON
(陳建民)(chairman)	O
Ms.	B-PERSON
HUANG	I-PERSON
Danhan	E-PERSON
(黃丹涵)	O
WANG	I-PERSON
Honggang	E-PERSON
(王洪剛)	O

Grandall	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Firm	I-ORG
(Shenzhen)	E-ORG
24,	O
31	O
&	O
41F,	O
Shenzhen	O
Special	O
Zone	O
Press	O
Tower	O
6008	O
Shennan	O
Blvd.	O
Shenzhen,	O
China	O
518034	O
Auditor	B-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Reporting	I-TITLE
Accountant	E-TITLE

Li,	B-PERSON
Yanmei	E-PERSON
(李妍梅)	O
.	O
Flat	O
38E,	O
Tower	O
1	O
Queen's	O
Terrace	O
Queen	O
Street	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

CMBC	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

China	B-ORG
Merchants	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Co.,	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
48/F.,	O
One	O
Exchange	O
Square	O
8	O
Connaught	O
Place	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Cayman	B-TITLE
Islands	I-TITLE
Principal	I-TITLE
Share	I-TITLE
Registrar	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Transfer	I-TITLE
Agent	E-TITLE
Conyers	B-ORG
Trust	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
(Cayman)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ng	I-PERSON
Cheuk	E-PERSON
Lun(吳卓倫)	O

Remuneration	O
committee	O
Mr.	O
Chan	O
Chi	O
Ming	O
Tony	O
(Chairman)	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Yan	I-PERSON
Xiaoqing	E-PERSON
(嚴曉晴)	O
No.	O
305,	O
Unit	O
1	O
Block	O
8,	O
Luofu	O
Shijia	O
8	O
Gaosheng	O
Qiaonan	O
Road	O
Wuhou	O
District,	O
Chengdu	O
China	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Xu	I-PERSON
Huijuan	E-PERSON
(徐惠娟)	O
No.	O
2	O
Nengyuan	O
Road	O
Tianhe	O
District	O
Guangzhou,	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Keung	I-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
Hung	E-PERSON
(姜國雄)	O
(Chairman)	O

Jun	B-ORG
He	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG

383	O
Madison	O
Avenue	O
New	O
York	O
NY	O
10179	O
Goldman	B-ORG
Sachs	I-ORG
(Asia)	I-ORG
L.L.C.	E-ORG

Independent	B-TITLE
industry	I-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE

AllBright	B-PERSON
Law	I-PERSON
Offices	I-PERSON
(Fuzhou)	E-PERSON
37th	O
Floor,	O
International	O
Financial	O
Center	O
No.1	O
Wanglong	O
2nd	O
Avenue	O
Taijiang	O
District	O
Fuzhou	O
350005	O
PRC	O

Internal	B-TITLE
control	I-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE
.	O
BT	B-ORG
Corporate	I-ORG
Governance	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
2/F,	O
625	O
King's	O
Road	O
North	O
Point	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

GF	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Brokerage	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O
for	O
purpose	O
of	O
SFO)	O

87	O
Industry	B-TITLE
Consultant	E-TITLE

Sir	B-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
Siu	I-PERSON
Man	E-PERSON
(郭兆文)	O
KR,	O
FCIS,	O
FCS	O
31/F.,	O
148	O
Electric	O
Road	O
North	O
Point,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Wu	I-PERSON
Daxiang	E-PERSON
(吳大香)	O
Room	O
1405,	O
Block	O
A	O
Lvjing	O
Xinyuan,	O
Phase	O
II	O
Shenzhen,	O
the	O
PRC	O

LI	B-PERSON
Ming	E-PERSON
(李明)	O
Room	O
401,	O
No.	O
13,	O
Lane	O
100	O
North	O
Linyi	O
Road	O
Pudong	O
New	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Li	I-PERSON
Haifeng	E-PERSON
(李海楓)	O
Room	O
B,	O
20th	O
Floor,	O
Tower	O
5	O
Leighton	O
Hill	O
2B	O
Broadwood	O
Road	O
Happy	O
Valley	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
ZHAI	I-PERSON
Fang	E-PERSON
(翟芳)	O
Room	O
2102,	O
Building	O
14	O
Central	O
Park	O
No.6	O
Chaoyangmenwai	O
Street	O
Chaoyang	O
District,	O
Beijing	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ng	I-PERSON
Sik	I-PERSON
Chiu	E-PERSON
(吳錫釗)	O
Flat	O
B,	O
9/F,	O
Block	O
4	O
Pacific	O
View	O
38	O
Tai	O
Tam	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Legal	B-TITLE
Adviser	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
our	I-TITLE
Company	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	I-ORG
Kong	E-ORG
law	O
William	B-ORG
Ji	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co.	E-ORG
in	O
Association	O
with	O
Tian	B-ORG
Yuan	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Firm	I-ORG
Office	E-ORG
Suite	O
702,	O
7/F	O
Two	O
Chinachem	O
Central	O
26	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
ZHANG	I-PERSON
Bingjun	E-PERSON
(張秉軍)	O
5-2-501	O
New	O
Century	O
City	O
Hexi	O
District	O
Tianjin	O
PRC	O

As	O
to	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
law:	O
Conyers	B-ORG
Dill	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Pearman	E-ORG
Cricket	O
Square	O
P.O.	O
Box	O
2681	O
Grand	O
KY1-1111	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wang	I-PERSON
Yingzhe	E-PERSON
(王英哲)	O
Room	O
102,	O
Unit	O
1,	O
Building	O
6	O
Middle	O
Siji	O
Xinghe	O
Road	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
Beijing	O
PRC	O

Internal	B-TITLE
control	I-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE
Corporate	B-ORG
Governance	I-ORG
Professionals	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(formerly	O
known	O
as	O
"Baker	O
Tilly	I-ORG
Hong	I-ORG
Kong	I-ORG
Risk	I-ORG
Assurance	E-ORG
Limited")	O
2nd	O
Floor	O
625	O
King's	O
Road	O
North	O
Point	O
Baker	B-ORG

Yang	B-PERSON
Yi	E-PERSON
(陽翼)	O
A306,	O
Zhouzhuan	O
Building	O
Jinan	O
University	O
601	O
Huangpu	O
Avenue	O
West	O
Guangzhou	O
PRC	O

Suites	O
4505–06,	O
45/F	O
Tower	O
1,	O
Lippo	O
Centre	O
89	O
Queensway	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
SFO)	O

Giraffe	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Joint	B-TITLE
company	I-TITLE
secretaries	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Chen	I-PERSON
Weibo	E-PERSON
(	O
陳衛波先生	O
)	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
TAM	I-PERSON
Pak	I-PERSON
Yu,	I-PERSON
Vivien	E-PERSON
(譚栢如)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Li	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON
Keung	E-PERSON
Flat	O
H,	O
2/F,	O
Block	O
2	O
Park	O
Mediterranean	O
9	O
Hong	O
Tsuen	O
Road	O
Sai	O
Kung	O
New	O
Territories	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
REN	I-PERSON
Jinsheng	E-PERSON
(任晉生)	O
Room	O
503,	O
Building	O
2	O
Haitang	O
Street,	O
Sunshine	O
Jubao	O
Villa	O
88	O
Xuanwu	O
Avenue,	O
District	O
Nanjing,	O
Jiangsu	O
PRC	O

Auditor	B-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
reporting	I-TITLE
accountant	E-TITLE
PricewaterhouseCoopers	B-ORG
Certified	O
Public	O
Accountants	O
Registered	O
Interest	O
Entity	O
22nd	O
Floor,	O
Prince's	O
Building	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Guoqi	B-PERSON
Ding	E-PERSON
丁国其	O
.	O
Room	O
1502,	O
No.18,	O
Lane	O
100	O
Yinxiao	O
Road	O
Pudongxin	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Zhang	I-PERSON
Jianhua	E-PERSON
(張建華)	O
.	O
Room	O
1001	O
No.	O
191	O
Yuxiu	O
Block	O
Siming	O
District	O
Xiamen	O
Fujian	O
Province	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Hung	I-PERSON
Ka	I-PERSON
Hai	I-PERSON
Clement	E-PERSON
(洪嘉禧先生)	O
House	O
25,	O
Casas	O
Domingo	O
No.	O
8	O
Kam	O
Street	O
Sheung	O
Shui	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
XIA	I-PERSON
Guisuo	E-PERSON
(夏貴所)	O
No.	O
2-16	O
6	O
Jiefang	O
South	O
Road	O
Yingze	O
District	O
Taiyuan	O
Shanxi	O
Province	O
the	O
PRC	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
Samantha	I-PERSON
Du	E-PERSON
No.	O
453,	O
Lane	O
1883	O
Hua	O
Mu	O
Road	O
Pudong	O
201204	O
Shanghai	O
China	O

Sánchez	O
Devanny	O
Eseverri,	O
S.C.	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinators,	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Bookrunners	E-TITLE
.	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
YU	I-PERSON
Yong	E-PERSON
(余勇)	O
Flat	O
301,	O
No.	O
67,	O
Block	O
18	O
Upper	O
House,	O
Haishu	O
District	O
Ningbo,	O
Zhejiang	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Joint	B-TITLE
company	I-TITLE
secretaries	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Ngai	I-PERSON
Fan	E-PERSON
HKICPA	O
Flat	O
G,	O
38/F,	O
Block	O
10	O
Grand	O
Yoho	O
Phase	O
1	O
9	O
Long	O
Yat	O
Road	O
Yuen	O
New	O
Territories,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

CORPORATE	B-SKIP
INFORMATIONName	I-SKIP
Address	I-SKIP
Nationality	E-SKIP

HK	B-ORG
Monkey	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
carrying	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
securities)	O
and	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Compliance	B-TITLE
adviser	E-TITLE
Shenwan	B-ORG
Hongyuan	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
(H.K.)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O

SG	B-ORG
Tax	I-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Pte.	I-ORG
Ltd.	E-ORG

Zinvest	B-ORG
Global	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
engage	O
in	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
securities),	O
2	O
futures	O
contracts),	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
securities)	O
and	O
5	O
contracts)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

PRC	O
Chinese	O
Non-Executive	B-TITLE
Director	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Yuan	I-PERSON
Shuntang	E-PERSON
(袁順唐)	O

Nomination	B-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Heung	I-PERSON
Che	E-PERSON
Kan(向志勤)	O
(Chairman)	O

As	O
to	O
PRC	O
law	O
Tian	B-ORG
Yuan	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Firm	E-ORG
10/F,	O
Tower	O
B,	O
China	O
Pacific	O
Insurance	O
Plaza	O
28	O
Fengsheng	O
Lane	O
Xicheng	O
District,	O
Beijing	O

LCH	B-ORG
(Asia-Pacific)	I-ORG
Surveyors	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
17th	O
Floor	O
Champion	O
Building	O
287-291	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Nomination	O
committee	O
Wong	O
Kwun	O
Ho	O
(黃冠豪)	O
(Chairman)	O

ICBC	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
37/F,	O
Tower	O
3	O
Garden	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Remuneration	O
committee	O
Ms.	O
Pan	O
Yingli	O
(潘英麗)	O
(Chairman)	O

Guo	B-PERSON
Shunshun	E-PERSON
(郭順順)	O
Room	O
1802,	O
Building	O
8	O
China	O
Railway	O
Construction	O
Haixi	O
199	O
Xiabao	O
Road	O
Siming	O
District	O
Xiamen	O
City	O
Fujian	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Industry	B-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE
Frost	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Sullivan	I-ORG
(Beijing)	I-ORG
Inc.,	I-ORG
Shanghai	I-ORG
Branch	I-ORG
Co.	E-ORG
Room	O
1018,	O
Tower	O
B	O
No.	O
500	O
Yunjin	O
Road	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
LIU	I-PERSON
Hon	I-PERSON
Por	I-PERSON
Francis	E-PERSON
(廖漢波)	O
FU	I-PERSON
Bradley	E-PERSON
(符基業)	O

Principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
in	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Unit	O
612,	O
6/F	O
CC	O
Wu	O
Building,	O
302-8	O
Hennessy	O
Road	O
Wan	O
Chai,	O

Zhang	B-PERSON
Changling	E-PERSON
(張長嶺)	O
73-9	O
Quyang	O
Main	O
Road	O
Town	O
Suiping	O
County	O
Henan	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Sponsors	E-TITLE
.	O

Co-Manager	S-TITLE
Conrad	B-ORG
Investment	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Qiyu	B-PERSON
Chen	I-PERSON
(	I-PERSON
Chairman	I-PERSON
)	E-PERSON
Jiemin	B-PERSON
Fu	E-PERSON
Yifang	B-PERSON
Wu	I-PERSON
Scott	E-PERSON
Shi-Kau	B-PERSON
Liu	I-PERSON
Aimin	E-PERSON
Hui	B-PERSON
Tak	B-PERSON
Young	I-PERSON
So	E-PERSON
Ruilin	B-PERSON
Song	E-PERSON
Audit	B-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
Lik	B-PERSON
Yuen	I-PERSON
Chan	E-PERSON
Xiaohui	B-PERSON
Guan	E-PERSON
Remuneration	B-TITLE

Further	O
information	O
on	O
the	O
Directors	O
is	O
disclosed	O
in	O
section	O
headed	O
"Directors	O
and	O
Senior	O
Management"	O
of	O
this	O
listing	O
document.	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Hung	I-PERSON
Ka	I-PERSON
Hai,	I-PERSON
Clement	E-PERSON
(洪嘉禧)	O
House	O
25,	O
Casas	O
Domingo	O
8	O
Kam	O
Street	O
Kwu	O
Tung	O
Sheung	O
Shui	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Canfield	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Name	B-SKIP
Residential	I-SKIP
address	I-SKIP
Nationality	I-SKIP
Executive	I-SKIP
Directors	E-SKIP

As	O
to	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
laws	O
Benny	B-ORG
Pang	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co	E-ORG
Solicitors,	O
27th	O
Floor,	O
100QRC	O
100	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Li	I-PERSON
Yuen	I-PERSON
Shan	E-PERSON
(李婉珊)	O
Flat	O
D,	O
26/F.,	O
Block	O
2	O
Liberte	O
No.	O
833	O
Lai	O
Chi	O
Kok	O
Road	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Li	I-PERSON
Zhiming	E-PERSON
No.	O
10-8-3,	O
Dong	O
Ting	O
Yi	O
Cun	O
Wuchang	O
District,	O
Wuhan,	O
Hubei	O
Province,	O
PRC	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
Tung	I-PERSON
LI,	I-PERSON
Donald,	I-PERSON
S.B.S.,	I-PERSON
J.P.	E-PERSON
(李國棟)	O
4th	O
Floor,	O
Block	O
K,	O
Pine	O
Court	O
5	O
Old	O
Peak	O
Road	O
Mid-levels	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Sponsor	E-TITLE
Lego	B-ORG
Corporate	I-ORG
Finance	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
Room	O
1601,	O
16/F	O
China	O
Building	O
29	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central,	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
John	I-PERSON
Diekman	E-PERSON
Ms.	B-PERSON
Nisa	I-PERSON
Leung	E-PERSON

Grand	B-ORG
China	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
permitted	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
Rm	O
503,	O
5/F,	O
Loke	O
Yew	O
Building	O
50–52	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Headquarters	O
and	O
principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
in	O
Singapore	O
10	O
Anson	O
Road	O
#21-02	O
International	O
Plaza	O
079903	O

WANG	B-PERSON
Yanyang	E-PERSON
(王艷陽)	O
.	O
Employee	O
Representative	O
Supervisor	O
Room	O
0604,	O
Building	O
No.	O
17	O
Wangyuan	O
Dongli	O
Fengtai	O
District	O
Beijing	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
WANG	I-PERSON
Ren	E-PERSON
(汪韌)	O
Flat	O
C3,	O
1/F	O
Repulse	O
Bay	O
Apartment	O
101	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Kingkey	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Group	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
44/F	O
Convention	O
Plaza	O
Office	O
Tower	O
1	O
Harbour	O
Road	O
Wan	O
Chai,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

As	O
to	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law:	O
Stephenson	B-ORG
Harwood	E-ORG
18th	O
Floor	O
United	O
Centre	O
95	O
Queensway	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Li	B-PERSON
Jinglian	E-PERSON
(栗景連)	O
(formerly	O
known	O
as	O
(栗景蓮))	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	E-TITLE
Macquarie	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Ms.	B-PERSON
Tan	I-PERSON
Pei	I-PERSON
Fung	E-PERSON
(陳旆芬)	O
(	O
Chairlady	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Yeo	O
Kwang	O
Maccann	O
(楊光)	O
Hon	O
Chin	O
Kheong	O
(Han	O
Zhenqiang)	O
(韓振強)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Fu	I-PERSON
Chun	I-PERSON
Keung	E-PERSON
(傅鎮強)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
57/F,	O
Block	O
1	O
Ocean	O
Pointe	O
8	O
Sham	O
Tsz	O
Street	O
Tseng	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ho	I-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
Lung	E-PERSON
(何國龍)	O

149	O
Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Morgan	B-ORG
Stanley	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Public	O
Offering	O
only)	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
Wong	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON
Wing	E-PERSON
(王志榮)	O
Flat	O
D,	O
20/F,	O
Block	O
2	O
Island	O
Harbourview	O
11	O
Hoi	O
Fai	O
Road	O
Kowloon	O
West	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Sponsor	E-TITLE
LY	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Rooms	O
1901–02	O
China	O
Insurance	O
Group	O
Building	O
141	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
as	O
defined	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Tan	I-PERSON
BS	E-PERSON
No.	O
20,	O
Jalan	O
Ponderosa	O
1/9	O
Taman	O
81100	O
Johor	O
Bahru	O
Johor,	O
Malaysia	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Zhou	I-PERSON
Guichang	E-PERSON
No.	O
201	O
South	O
Zhonghua	O
Road	O
Nanming	O
District	O
Guiyang,	O
Guizhou	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
ABCI	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
regulated	O
activities	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Wong	I-PERSON
Han	I-PERSON
Yu	I-PERSON
Alice	E-PERSON
(王嫻俞)	O
Unit	O
4501	O
Tower	O
2,	O
Shimao	O
Riveria	O
Garden	O
Lane	O
Wai	O
Fang	O
West	O
Road	O
New	O
Pudong	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
the	O
PRC*	O

802-804	O
Champion	O
Tower	O
3	O
Garden	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
as	O
to	O
PRC	O
law:	O

Legal	B-TITLE
Advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	E-TITLE
as	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law:	O


Joint	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinators	E-TITLE
ICBC	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

151	O
Lorong	O
Chuan	O
#04-03A	O
New	O
Tech	O
Park	O
Singapore	O
556741	O
Place	O
of	O
Business	O
in	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Registered	O
under	O
Part	O
16	O
the	O
Companies	O
Ordinance	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Yanling	I-PERSON
Cao	E-PERSON
(曹彥凌)	O
16/F,	O
Tower	O
5,	O
Bel	O
Air	O
On	O
the	O
Peak	O
Island	O
South	O
(Phase	O
IV),	O
68	O
Avenue,	O
Pok	O
Fu	O
Lam,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Shen	I-PERSON
Min	E-PERSON
(沈敏),	O
whose	O
former	O
name	O
was	O
Xiaodu	O
(沈筱度)	O
(Chairman)	O

Co-Lead	B-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Red	B-ORG
Eagle	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Differ	B-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
conduct	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activities	O

Senior	B-TITLE
Management	E-TITLE

YANG	B-PERSON
Wenqing	E-PERSON
(楊文清)	O
.	O
Executive	O
Director,	O
Vice	O
Chairman	O
Room	O
1604,	O
Building	O
No.	O
12	O
Chunshu	O
Yuan,	O
Xicheng	O
District	O
Beijing	O

As	O
to	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law	O
H.M.	B-ORG
Chan	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co	E-ORG
in	O
association	O
with	O
Taylor	B-ORG
Wessing	E-ORG

Compliance	B-TITLE
adviser	E-TITLE
Kingsway	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
7/F,	O
Tower	O
1	O
Lippo	O
Centre	O
89	O
Queensway	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinator,	I-TITLE
Bookrunner,	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Manager	I-TITLE

Headquarters	O
and	O
principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
255	O
Pandan	O
Loop	O
Singapore	O
128433	O

Registered	O
office	O
P.O.	O
Box	O
309	O
Ugland	O
House	O
Grand	O
Cayman	O
KY1-1104	O
Islands	O

Cushman	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Wakefield	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Keng	I-PERSON
Stephen	E-PERSON
Lee(李青松)	O
(formerly	O
known	O
as	O
Li	B-PERSON
Ching	E-PERSON
Chung(李青松))	O
Lee	I-PERSON
Chung	I-PERSON

Ms.	B-PERSON
Leung	I-PERSON
Suet	I-PERSON
Wing	E-PERSON
(梁雪穎)	O
36/F,	O
Tower	O
Two,	O
Times	O
Square	O
1	O
Matheson	O
Street	O
Causeway	O
Bay,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Easy	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
11/F	O
Continental	O
Place	O
238	O
Dex	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Sheung	O
Wan	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Chong	B-PERSON
Man	I-PERSON
Hung	I-PERSON
Jeffrey	E-PERSON
Flat	O
E	O
48/F	O
Tower	O
15	O
88	O
O	O
King	O
Road,	O
Phase	O
3	O
Ocean	O
Shores	O
Tseung	O
Kwan	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Property	O
Valuer	O
Savills	O
Valuation	O
and	O
Professional	O
Services	O
(S)	O
Pte	O
Ltd	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Carlyon	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
E	O
22/F	O
Tower	O
A	O
Billion	O
Centre	O
1	O
Wang	O
Kwong	O
Road	O
Kowloon	O
Bay	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
JIN	I-PERSON
Haiteng	E-PERSON
(金海騰)	O
Room	O
202,	O
Unit	O
1,	O
Building	O
16	O
Renshou	O
Hill	O
West	O
Lake	O
District	O
Hangzhou	O
Zhejiang	O
Province	O
the	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
TONG	I-PERSON
Weiliang	E-PERSON
(童瑋亮)	O
.	O
No.	O
305,	O
Building	O
4	O
No.37,	O
Gupinggang	O
Gulou	O
District	O
Nanjing	O
City	O
Jiangsu	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Gary	I-PERSON
Ng	I-PERSON
Sin	I-PERSON
Tong	E-PERSON
(alias	O
Huang	E-PERSON
Chendong)	O
(黃晨東先生)	O
15	O
Yio	O
Chu	O
Kang	O
Drive	O
Singapore	O
786286	O
Singaporean	O
Chendong	O

TMF	B-ORG
Hong	I-ORG
Kong	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
31/F,	O
Tower	O
Two,	O
Times	O
Square	O
1	O
Matheson	O
Street,	O
Causeway	O
Bay	O

Merdeka	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Richard	I-PERSON
Antony	E-PERSON
Bennett	O
.	O
26	O
Bristol	O
Road	O
Brighton	O
BN2	O
1AP	O
United	O
Kingdom	O

Legal	B-TITLE
advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law	O
Deacons	S-ORG
5th	O
Floor	O
Alexandra	O
House	O
18	O
Chater	O
Road	O
Central	O

The	O
Right	O
Honorable	O
Sir	B-PERSON
Hugo	I-PERSON
George	I-PERSON
William	E-PERSON
Swire,	O
KCMG,	O
MP	O
(Chairman)	O
Swire	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Leung	I-PERSON
Shui	I-PERSON
Bing	E-PERSON

Legal	B-TITLE
adviser	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sponsor,	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinator,	I-TITLE
Joint	I-TITLE
Bookrunners,	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	I-TITLE

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lau	I-PERSON
Koong	I-PERSON
Yep	E-PERSON
(劉冠業先生)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
40/F,	O
Block	O
8	O
Park	O
Central	O
No.9	O
Tong	O
Tak	O
Street	O
Tseung	O
Kwan	O
O,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

73	O
Legal	B-TITLE
advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
our	I-TITLE
Company	E-TITLE

Jones	B-PERSON
Day	E-PERSON
31/F,	O
Edinburgh	O
Tower	O
The	O
Landmark	O
15	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Citigroup	B-ORG
Global	I-ORG
Markets	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Public	O
Offering	O
only)	O
50/F,	O
Champion	O
Tower	O
3	O
Garden	O
Road	O

Company	B-TITLE
secretary	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Shum	I-PERSON
Hoi	I-PERSON
Luen	E-PERSON
(沈凱聯)	O
Certified	O
Public	O
Accountant	O
Room	O
2205,	O
22/F	O
On	O
Hong	O
Commercial	O
Building	O
145	O
Hennessy	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Kong	O

Registered	O
office	O
in	O
the	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
PO	O
Box	O
1350,	O
Clifton	O
House	O
75	O
Fort	O
Street,	O
Grand	O
KY1-1108	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
GUOBIN	I-PERSON
ZHANG	E-PERSON
(張國斌)	O
35	O
Amber	O
Gardens	O
#15-09	O
Singapore	O
439966	O
Singaporean	O

Property	B-TITLE
valuer	E-TITLE
Cushman	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Wakefield	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

FUNG	B-PERSON
Edwin	E-PERSON
(馮冠豪)	O
C2209	O
Yosemite	O
Villa	O
Houshayu	O
Area	O
Shunyi	O
District	O
Beijing	O
PRC	O

Zhu	B-PERSON
Li	E-PERSON
(朱力)	O
Room	O
901,	O
Unit	O
1,	O
Building	O
5,	O
District	O
5	O
Xidi	O
International	O
City	O
128	O
Hengshan	O
Road	O
Nanjing,	O
Jiangsu	O
Province	O
The	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Xu	I-PERSON
Jianhai	E-PERSON
(徐建海)	O
Room	O
201,	O
No.	O
6,	O
Alley	O
368	O
Fengzhou	O
Road,	O
Malu	O
Town	O
Jiading	O
District,	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Compliance	B-TITLE
adviser	E-TITLE
Guotai	B-ORG
Junan	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
6	O
(advising	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
as	O
defined	O
in	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Yu	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON
Wei	E-PERSON
(余志威先生)	O
Flat	O
1,	O
8/F.,	O
Block	O
B	O
Golden	O
Lion	O
Garden	O
Phase	O
One	O
5	O
Chui	O
Tin	O
Street	O
Tai	O
Wai,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Legal	B-TITLE
advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriter(s)	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law:	O
Charltons	S-ORG
12/F,	O
Dominion	O
Centre	O
43-59	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
East	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Bookrunner	E-TITLE
Sunfund	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
18th	O
Floor,	O
Hip	O
Shing	O
Hong	O
Centre	O
55	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Kong	O
Licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
engage	O
in	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
of	O
regulated	O
activities	O
as	O
defined	O

Alpha	B-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Group	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Compliance	B-TITLE
Adviser	E-TITLE
Anglo	B-ORG
Chinese	I-ORG
Corporate	I-ORG
Finance,	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Luk	B-ORG
Fook	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Units	O
502–6,	O
5/F,	O
Low	O
Block	O
Grand	O
Millennium	O
Plaza	O
181	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
permitted	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
4	O
(advising	O
securities)	O
and	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
for	O
purpose	O
of	O
SFO)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Kang	I-PERSON
Woon	E-PERSON
(康洹)	O
Flat	O
D,	O
G/F,	O
Tower	O
6	O
Grandeur	O
Road,	O
Parc	O
Oasis	O
Yau	O
Yat	O
Chuen,	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Maples	B-ORG
Corporate	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
P.O.	O
Box	O
309,	O
Ugland	O
House	O
Grand	O
Cayman,	O
KY1-1104	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chen	I-PERSON
Shuo	E-PERSON
(陳碩)	O
Wei	O
Hai	O
Yan	O
(魏海燕)	O

Lim	B-PERSON
Sooi	I-PERSON
Kheng	I-PERSON
Patrick	E-PERSON
(林瑞慶)	O
.	O
Block	O
3	O
Holland	O
Close	O
#22-53	O
Singapore	O
271003	O
Singaporean	O

Cricket	O
Square,	O
Hutchins	O
Drive	O
PO	O
Box	O
2681	O
Grand	O
Cayman,	O
KY1-1111	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chu	I-PERSON
Hoe	I-PERSON
Tin	E-PERSON
(朱浩天)	O
Flat	O
C,	O
26/F.,	O
Tower	O
1,	O
The	O
Sparkle	O
500	O
Tung	O
Chau	O
Street,	O
Cheung	O
Sha	O
Wan	O
Kowloon,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ting	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON
Wai	I-PERSON
Roy	E-PERSON
(丁志威先生)	O
House	O
80	O
The	O
Vineyard	O
Mouton	O
Avenue	O
Ngan	O
Tam	O
Mei	O
Yuen	O
Long,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lim	I-PERSON
Peng	I-PERSON
Chuan	I-PERSON
Terence	E-PERSON
(Chairman)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Victor	I-PERSON
Huang	E-PERSON
(黃偉德)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
6/F,	O
Block	O
9	O
Braemar	O
Hill	O
Mansion	O
31	O
Road	O
North	O
Point	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Heung	I-PERSON
Yue	I-PERSON
Wing	E-PERSON
(向裕永)	O
8/F,	O
Harita	O
Court	O
199	O
Prince	O
Edward	O
Road	O
West	O
Kowloon	O
City	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Gong	I-PERSON
Lijin	E-PERSON
(龔麗瑾)	O
Unit	O
1,	O
No.	O
50	O
Building	O
Guojicun	O
District,	O
Xuefengxi	O
Road	O
Siji	O
Community,	O
Beiyuan	O
Street	O
Yiwu	O
City,	O
Jinhua	O
City	O
Zhejiang	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Sze	I-PERSON
Irons	I-PERSON
B.B.S.,	I-PERSON
JP	E-PERSON
(施榮懷)	O
Flat	O
A1,	O
16/F	O
Summit	O
Court	O
144	O
Tin	O
Hau	O
Temple	O
Road	O
North	O
Point,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

ABCI	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited,	E-ORG
or	O
(Joint	O
Bookrunner	O
only)	O

NG	B-PERSON
Shung	E-PERSON
(吳嵩),	O
JP	O
(Australia)	O

44/F,	O
Convention	O
Plaza	O
Office	O
Tower	O
1	O
Harbour	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
regulated	O
activities)	O

Legal	B-TITLE
advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Company	E-TITLE
as	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
laws	O
Wong,	B-ORG
Wan	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Partners	E-ORG
in	O
Association	O
with	O
Seyfarth	B-ORG
Shaw	E-ORG
Suite	O
3701,	O
Edinburgh	O
Tower	O
The	O
Landmark	O
15	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Singapore	O
Allen	O
Gledhill	O
LLP	O
One	O
Marina	O
Boulevard	O
#28-00	O
018989	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
Appleby	O
2206–19	O
Jardine	O
House	O
1	O
Connaught	O
Place	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ken	I-PERSON
Kwok	E-PERSON
(郭君宇)	O
6	O
Eighteenth	O
Street	O
Hong	O
Lok	O
Yuen	O
Tai	O
Po,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Kong	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Liang	I-PERSON
Jiexin	E-PERSON
No.	O
44	O
East	O
Second	O
Street	O
Dongfeng	O
Town	O
Zhongshan	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Tsang	I-PERSON
Ka	I-PERSON
Yip	I-PERSON
Sze	I-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
Wing	I-PERSON
Nigel	E-PERSON

Realord	B-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Pacific	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
permitted	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
Suite	O
2402,	O
24/F,	O
Jardine	O
House	O
Connaught	O
Place	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Wang	B-PERSON
Xiaoying	E-PERSON
(王小英)	O
No.	O
7,	O
4/F,	O
Unit	O
4,	O
Building	O
1	O
17	O
Jinsha	O
Road	O
West	O
Lane	O
Jinniu	O
District,	O
Chengdu	O
Sichuan	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Frost	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Sullivan	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Sun	I-PERSON
Jie	E-PERSON
(孫杰)	O
(Chairman)	O

Kaisa	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Rooms	O
2011–12	O
20/F,	O
Two	O
International	O
Finance	O
Centre	O
No.	O
8	O
Street,	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
A	O
licenced	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chu	I-PERSON
Kin	I-PERSON
Ming	E-PERSON
(朱健明)	O
Flat	O
C,	O
11/F.,	O
Tower	O
1	O
Heya	O
Aqua,	O
Cheung	O
Sha	O
Wan	O
Kowloon,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
ZHANG	I-PERSON
Hongshi	E-PERSON
Room	O
1901,	O
Greenfield	O
Tower	O
Concordia	O
Plaza	O
1	O
Science	O
Museum	O
Road	O
Tsim	O
Sha	O
Tsui	O
East	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

ABCI	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(in	O
the	O
capacity	O
as	O
a	O
Joint	O
Lead	O
Manager)	O
10/F,	O
Agricultural	O
Bank	O
of	O
China	O
Tower	O
50	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
HOU	I-PERSON
Min	E-PERSON
(侯珉)	O
No.	O
1,	O
Room	O
2,	O
14/F	O
8	O
Huang	O
Tu	O
Bo	O
Heung	O
Shan	O
Nan	O
Road	O
Hai	O
Dian	O
District	O
Beijing	O
PRC	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
SIN	I-PERSON
Wai	I-PERSON
Chiu	I-PERSON
Joseph	E-PERSON
(冼偉超博士)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
19/F.,	O
Block	O
2	O
Julimount	O
Garden	O
8	O
–	O
12	O
Fu	O
Kin	O
Street	O
Shatin	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chia	I-PERSON
Kok	I-PERSON
Seng	E-PERSON
(謝國成先生)	O
31	O
Lentor	O
Grove	O
Singapore	O
789205	O
Singaporean	O

Head	O
office	O
and	O
principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
PRC	O
No.	O
4	O
Meide	O
Street	O
Meigui	O
Zone	O
Industrial	O
Park	O
Pingyin	O
County	O
Jinan	O
Shandong	O
Province	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chiu	I-PERSON
Wai	I-PERSON
Kwong	E-PERSON
(趙維光先生)	O
Flat	O
C,	O
21st	O
Floor	O
Tower	O
2,	O
The	O
Parkside	O
18	O
Tong	O
Chun	O
Street	O
Tseung	O
Kwan	O
O	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Citigroup	B-ORG
Global	I-ORG
Markets	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(Joint	O
Bookrunner	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
International	O
Offering	O
only)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wan	I-PERSON
Ho	I-PERSON
Yin	I-PERSON
Guo	I-PERSON
Shaomu	E-PERSON
Ms.	B-PERSON
Tang	I-PERSON
Lo	I-PERSON
Nar	E-PERSON

Innovax	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
2002	O
20/F,	O
Chinachem	O
Century	O
Tower	O
178	O
Gloucester	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Sidley	B-ORG
Austin	E-ORG
Level	O
39,	O
Two	O
International	O
Finance	O
Centre	O
8	O
Street	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

CCB	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Joint	B-TITLE
auditors	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
reporting	I-TITLE
accountants	E-TITLE
*	O
Mazars	B-ORG
CPA	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Sun	B-PERSON
Zhaolin	E-PERSON
(孫兆林)	O
A1-5	O
Hongyu	O
Wanhao	O
Garden	O
Fushun	O
Liaoning	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
GUO	I-PERSON
Dongxu	E-PERSON
(郭東旭先生)	O
(Vice	O
Chairman	O
and	O
Vice	O
President)	O
B1201	O
Building	O
7,	O
Haojianglijing	O
Haojiang	O
Road	O
Shishi	O
City	O
Fujian	O
Province	O
China	O

Allen	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Overy	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chen	I-PERSON
Bin	E-PERSON
(陳彬)	O
Room	O
610,	O
Unit	O
1,	O
Block	O
33	O
Dongdi	O
Garden	O
Liqizhuang	O
Street	O
Xiqing	O
District	O
Tianjin,	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Yip	I-PERSON
Koon	I-PERSON
Shing	E-PERSON
(葉冠成)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
13/F	O
Princess	O
Court	O
9	O
King	O
Tak	O
Street	O
Ho	O
Man	O
Tin,	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

BOA	B-ORG
MS	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Mak	I-PERSON
Hing	I-PERSON
Keung,	I-PERSON
Thomas	E-PERSON
(麥興強)	O
(Chairman)	O
Ding	I-PERSON
Zaiguo	E-PERSON
(丁再國)	O
Ms.	B-PERSON
Zhang	I-PERSON
Lanrong	E-PERSON
(張嵐嶸)	O

Independent	B-TITLE
registered	I-TITLE
safety	I-TITLE
auditor	E-TITLE
Tse	B-PERSON
Wing	I-PERSON
Ning	E-PERSON

Dr.	B-PERSON
PAUL	I-PERSON
HERBERT	I-PERSON
CHEW	E-PERSON
1	O
Brookdale	O
Dr	O
Lawrenceville	O
NJ	O
08648-5545	O
United	O
States	O
of	O
America	O

3333	O
Peachtree	O
Road	O
Ne,	O
9th	O
Floor	O
Atlanta,	O
GA	O
30326	O
United	O
States	O
of	O
America	O

As	O
to	O
PRC	O
law	O
Shu	B-ORG
Jin	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Firm	E-ORG
12/F,	O
Taiping	O
Finance	O
Tower	O
6001	O
Yitian	O
Road,	O
Futian	O
District	O
Shenzhen,	O
China	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Ho	I-PERSON
Sze	I-PERSON
Man	I-PERSON
Kristie	E-PERSON
(何思敏)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
23rd	O
Floor	O
Tower	O
3,	O
Island	O
Garden	O
33	O
Chai	O
Wan	O
Road	O
Shau	O
Kei	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Upmax	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
1717,	O
China	O
Merchants	O
Tower	O
Shun	O
Tak	O
Centre	O
168	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
as	O
defined	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Legal	B-TITLE
Advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
our	I-TITLE
Company	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law:	O
Stevenson,	B-ORG
Wong	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co.	E-ORG
39/F,	O
Gloucester	O
Tower	O
The	O
Landmark	O
15	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ng	I-PERSON
Sheung	I-PERSON
Chung	E-PERSON
Flat	O
B,	O
10/F,	O
Chinese	O
(伍尚聰)	O
Hoi	O
Ning	O
Mansion	O
(Block	O
17)	O

Remuneration	O
committee	O
Gu	O
Jianlu	O
(顧劍璐)	O
(Chairman)	O

Zhang	B-PERSON
Dongmin	E-PERSON
(張冬敏)	O
------	O
10-1	O
Duozi	O
Xiang,	O
Qingyang	O
District,	O
Chengdu,	O
PRC	O

Registered	O
office.	O
.	O
Cricket	O
Square	O
Hutchins	O
Drive	O
P.O.	O
Box	O
2681	O
Grand	O
Cayman	O
KY1-1111	O
Islands	O

ZHOU	B-PERSON
Zheren	E-PERSON
(周喆人)	O
Block	O
20,	O
Hongmei	O
Villa	O
2989	O
Road	O
Minhang	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Elstone	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

CFN	B-TITLE
Lawyers	E-TITLE
in	O
association	O
with	O
Broad	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Bright	E-ORG
27th	O
Floor,	O
Neich	O
Tower	O
128	O
Gloucester	O
Road	O
Wan	O
Chai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Yuan	B-PERSON
Jun	E-PERSON
Room	O
5c,	O
Block	O
3	O
Yuhu	O
Bay	O
Garden	O
Xixiang	O
Road	O
Baoan	O
District	O
Shenzhen,	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
PRC	O

As	O
to	O
Netherlands	O
law:	O
Rutgers	O
Posch	O
Visée	O
Endedijk	O
N.V.	O
Herengracht	O
466,	O
1017	O
CA	O
Amsterdam	O
P.O.	O
Box	O
10896	O
1001	O
EW	O
The	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
YEUNG	I-PERSON
Tze	I-PERSON
Long	E-PERSON
(楊子朗)	O
Grace	O
Terrace	O
No.	O
75	O
Yeung	O
Uk	O
Tsuen	O
Au	O
Tau,	O
Yuen	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Hui	I-PERSON
Yan	I-PERSON
Kit	E-PERSON
(許人傑先生)	O
Flat	O
B,	O
20/F,	O
Block	O
5	O
Parc	O
Royale	O
Shatin,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

As	O
to	O
PRC	O
law	O
Tahota	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Firm	E-ORG
16th	O
Floor,	O
Palm	O
Springs	O
International	O
Centre	O
No.	O
199,	O
Middle	O
of	O
Tianfu	O
Avenue	O
High-tech	O
District,	O
Chengdu	O
(610041)	O

Legal	B-TITLE
advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
U.S.	O
laws	O
Norton	B-ORG
Rose	I-ORG
Fulbright	E-ORG

Legal	B-TITLE
advisors	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
our	I-TITLE
Company	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law:	O
Sidley	B-ORG
Austin	E-ORG
Level	O
39	O
Two	O
International	O
Finance	O
Centre	O
8	O
Street	O
Central	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
BOCOM	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Nomination	O
committee	O
of	O
the	O
Board	O
Mr.	O
Tan	O
Chee	O
Beng	O
(Chairman)	O
Leung	O
Kee	O
Wai	O
(梁基偉)	O
Wee	O
Chorng	O
Kien	O

18/F-19/F	O
China	O
Building,	O
29	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
2	O
futures	O
contracts),	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
6	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
and	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Manager	E-TITLE
First	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
TANG	I-PERSON
Xin	E-PERSON
(湯欣)	O
No.143,	O
Block	O
Northwestern	O
1,	O
Tsinghua	O
University,	O
Haidian	O
District,	O
Beijing,	O
PRC	O

Reporting	B-TITLE
accountants	E-TITLE
Deloitte	B-ORG
Touche	I-ORG
Tohmatsu	E-ORG
Certified	O
Public	O
Accountants	O
35th	O
Floor,	O
One	O
Pacific	O
Place	O
88	O
Queensway	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

SBI	B-ORG
China	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
A2,	O
32/F	O
United	O
Centre	O
95	O
Queensway	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Room	O
A,	O
17/F	O
Fortune	O
House	O
61	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central,	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities)	O

28th	O
Floor,	O
Chater	O
House	O
8	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
J.P.	B-ORG
Morgan	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
plc	E-ORG
(in	O
relation	O
to	O
International	O
Offering)	O

John	B-PERSON
WU	I-PERSON
Jiong	E-PERSON
SHANG	B-PERSON
Jian	E-PERSON

Citigroup	B-ORG
Global	I-ORG
Markets	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
50/F	O
Champion	O
Tower	O
Three	O
Garden	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Industry	B-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE
Frost	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Sullivan	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
1706,	O
One	O
Exchange	O
Square	O
8	O
Connaught	O
Place	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Barrister-at-law	O
of	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
10/F,	O
Grand	O
Building	O
15–18	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
BOCI	B-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Registered	O
office	O
c/o	O
Walkers	B-ORG
Corporate	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Cayman	O
Centre	O
27	O
Hospital	O
Road,	O
George	O
Town	O
Grand	O
Cayman,	O
KY1-9008	O
Islands	O

HUANG	B-PERSON
Qi	E-PERSON
(黃琦)	O
.	O
Employee	O
Representative	O
Supervisor	O
Room	O
801,	O
Unit	O
1	O
Building	O
No.6,	O
Court	O
16	O
Xinhuali	O
Xicheng	O
District	O
Beijing	O

Sinomax	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Audit	O
committee	O
Mr.	O
Tan	O
Eng	O
Ann	O
(Chairman)	O
Chung	O
Kwok	O
Hoe	O
Lee	O
Shy	O
Tsong	O

Company	B-TITLE
secretary	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Chiu	I-PERSON
Wai	I-PERSON
Kwong	E-PERSON
Certified	O
Public	O
Accountant	O
Flat	O
C,	O
21st	O
Floor	O
Tower	O
2,	O
The	O
Parkside	O
18	O
Tong	O
Chun	O
Street	O
Tseung	O
Kwan	O
O,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Vision	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Holdings	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mak	B-PERSON
Po	I-PERSON
Man	I-PERSON
Cherie	E-PERSON
(麥寶文)	O
(ACCA,	O
CPA,	O
ACIS,	O
ACS,	O
MCG)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wang	I-PERSON
Wei	E-PERSON
(王偉)	O
2401	O
Building	O
2	O
Yijiajiayuan,	O
No.	O
8	O
Yard	O
Tonghui	O
South	O
Road	O
Tongzhou	O
District	O
Beijing	O
PRC	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Representatives	E-TITLE
Huatai	B-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Holdings	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Avenida	O
da	O
Amizade	O
555	O
–	O
Macau	O
Landmark	O
Office	O
Tower	O
23rd	O
Floor	O

Hung	B-ORG
Sing	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
2505,	O
25/F	O
West	O
Tower	O
Shun	O
Tak	O
Centre	O
200	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Unit	O
7801	O
–	O
7803,	O
78/F	O
The	O
Centre	O
99	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
conduct	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
(as	O
defined	O
SFO))	O

Wealth	B-ORG
Link	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

10	O
Lamartine	O
Caddesi	O
Taksim	O
34437	O
lstanbul	O
Turkey	O
As	O
to	O
Mexican	O
law:	O

CHEN	B-PERSON
Wen	E-PERSON
(陳文)	O
No.	O
999	O
Zhongshan	O
West	O
Road	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Ruibang	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
and	O
permitted	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
of	O
regulated	O
activities	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lai	I-PERSON
Man	I-PERSON
Shun	E-PERSON
(黎萬信)	O
1/F,	O
Rear	O
Portion	O
48	O
Cheung	O
Sha	O
Wan	O
Road	O
Sham	O
Shui	O
Po	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Industry	B-TITLE
Consultant	E-TITLE
Shanghai	B-ORG
iResearch	I-ORG
Co.,	I-ORG
Ltd	E-ORG
R701	O
Tower	O
B	O
Zhongjin	O
International	O
Caoxi	O
North	O
No.333	O
Xuhui	O
District	O
Shanghai,	O
200030	O
Receiving	B-TITLE
Banks	E-TITLE
Bank	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
China	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
1	O
Garden	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ren	I-PERSON
Xuefeng	E-PERSON
(任雪峰)	O
Unit	O
909,	O
Building	O
1,	O
No.	O
76	O
Sanhuan	O
West	O
Road	O
Haidian	O
District,	O
Beijing,	O
China	O
Chinese	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Jianping	I-PERSON
HUA	E-PERSON
917,	O
29	O
On	O
Chun	O
Street	O
Ma	O
Shan	O
Sha	O
Tin,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Yu	I-PERSON
Weijun	E-PERSON
(余偉俊)	O
Room	O
702,	O
No.	O
128	O
Dai	O
Yuan,	O
81	O
Xian	O
Lie	O
Zhong	O
Road,	O
Yuexiu	O
District,	O
Guangzhou,	O
PRC	O

Principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
PRC	O
Building	O
18,	O
Scientific	O
Park	O
Suhua	O
No.	O
208	O
Tongyuan	O
Road,	O
Suzhou	O
Industrial	O
Jiangsu	O
Province	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
FENG	I-PERSON
Jiankuan	E-PERSON
(馮建寬)	O
3-2-101	O
Haiyichangzhou	O
Hanjingyuan	O
Suijiang	O
Road	O
Hexi	O
District	O
Tianjin	O
PRC	O

Livermore	B-ORG
Holdings	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
Unit	O
1214A,	O
12/F	O
Tower	O
II	O
Cheung	O
Sha	O
Wan	O
Plaza	O
833	O
Road	O
Kowloon,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

SBI	B-ORG
China	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Dong	I-PERSON
Xiaolin	E-PERSON
(董小麟)	O
Room	O
702,	O
Block	O
3	O
641	O
Zhongdapu	O
Garden	O
Haizhu	O
District	O
Guangzhou	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Grand	B-ORG
China	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
carrying	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Yu	I-PERSON
Erhao	E-PERSON
(余尔好)	O
Flat	O
C,	O
11/F	O
Tower	O
1,	O
Phase	O
Ocean	O
Shores	O
88	O
O	O
King	O
Road	O
Tseung	O
Kwan	O
O,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

As	O
to	O
PRC	O
laws:	O
Fangda	B-ORG
Partners	E-ORG
27/F,	O
North	O
Tower	O
Beijing	O
Kerry	O
Centre	O
1	O
Guanghua	O
Road	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
Beijing,	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
ZHANG	I-PERSON
Yanyan	E-PERSON
(張妍妍)	O
3/F,	O
Unit	O
5,	O
Building	O
108	O
Wangjing	O
East	O
Garden	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
Beijing,	O
PRC	O

Industry	B-TITLE
consultants	E-TITLE
Converging	B-ORG
Knowledge	I-ORG
Pte.	I-ORG
Ltd.	E-ORG

Xing	B-PERSON
Liu	E-PERSON
劉星	O
Flat	O
B,	O
51/F,	O
Block	O
T5	O
South	O
Towers	O
Bel-Air	O
Phase	O
2	O
38	O
Avenue	O
Cyber	O
Port,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Lead	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
A,	O
23/F,	O
The	O
Wellington	O
198	O
Street	O
Sheung	O
Wan	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
A	O
licenced	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
PRC	O
No.	O
18	O
Shiwei	O
Pinggang	O
Industrial	O
Zone	O
Jiangshi	O
community,	O
Gongming	O
Street	O
Guangming	O
New	O
District	O
Shenzhen,	O
Guangdong	O
China	O

GONG	B-PERSON
Yingying	E-PERSON
(宮盈盈)	O
.	O
Unit	O
3101,	O
Building	O
No.	O
2	O
Guang	O
Hua	O
Xi	O
Li	O
1	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
Beijing	O
China	O

Company	B-TITLE
secretary	E-TITLE
Ms.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Lok	I-PERSON
Yee(陳濼而),	E-PERSON
ACS	O

18	O
Old	O
Peak	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Chinese	O
Non-executive	O
Directors	O

Principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
PRC	O
1209,	O
1211,	O
1213,	O
1215,	O
1217,	O
1219	O
Guangyin	O
Building	O
No.	O
38,	O
Futian	O
South	O
Road	O
Huanggang	O
Port	O
District	O
Shenzhen	O

Tobias	B-ORG
Benjamin	I-ORG
Hekster	E-ORG
1336	O
Washington	O
Avenue	O
Wilmette,	O
IL	O
60091	O
The	O
USA	O

Legal	B-TITLE
advisors	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor,	I-TITLE
Joint	I-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinators	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	E-TITLE
.	O

Headquarters	O
and	O
Principal	O
Place	O
of	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
U.S.	O
.	O
1420	O
Lakeside	O
Parkway	O
Suite	O
110	O
Flower	O
Mound	O
Texas	O
75028-4035	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Rao	I-PERSON
Ye	E-PERSON
Room	O
2405,	O
Building	O
3	O
Junfacheng	O
Baiheyuan	O
Panlong	O
District,	O
Kunming	O
Yunnan,	O
PRC	O

ChaoShang	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Rooms	O
2206-2210,	O
22/F.	O
China	O
Resources	O
Building	O
26	O
Harbour	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Fortune	B-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
43/F,	O
COSCO	O
Tower	O
183	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

As	O
to	O
Malaysia	O
law:	O
Jeff	B-ORG
Leong,	I-ORG
Poon	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Wong	E-ORG
Advocates	O
and	O
solicitors,	O
B-11–8,	O
Level	O
11	O
Megan	O
Avenue	O
II	O
Jalan	O
Yap	O
Kwan	O
Seng	O
50450	O
Kuala	O
Lumpur	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ng	I-PERSON
Seng	I-PERSON
Leong	E-PERSON
Flat	O
A,	O
11/F	O
Fulham	O
Garden	O
84	O
Pok	O
Fu	O
Lam	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Fortune	B-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
a	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
43rd	O
Floor,	O
Cosco	O
Tower	O
183	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Soochow	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
International	I-ORG
Brokerage	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Gu	I-PERSON
Yunchang	E-PERSON
Ms.	B-PERSON
Kan	I-PERSON
Lai	I-PERSON
Kuen,	I-PERSON
Alice	E-PERSON

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
.	O
Zhongtai	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
19/F.,	O
Li	O
Po	O
Chun	O
Chambers	O
189	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Leung	B-PERSON
Yee	I-PERSON
Tak	E-PERSON
(梁以德)	O
9/F,	O
114	O
Argyle	O
Street	O
Ho	O
Man	O
Tin,	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
WANG	I-PERSON
Song	E-PERSON
(王松)	O
No.14-901,	O
Hexie	O
Garden	O
Huancui	O
District	O
Weihai	O
City	O
Shandong	O
Province	O
the	O
PRC	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Chen	I-PERSON
Zhimin	E-PERSON
(陳智敏)	O
1-1103	O
Hongsong	O
Court,	O
Green	O
Garden	O
Xihu	O
District	O
Hangzhou,	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
LI	I-PERSON
Jiaqing	E-PERSON
(李家慶)	O
Room	O
302	O
Lane	O
888	O
No.	O
8	O
Jinxiu	O
Road	O
Shanghai	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Zhao	I-PERSON
Weihao	E-PERSON
(趙偉豪)	O
Room	O
601,	O
Building	O
no.	O
1	O
No.	O
7	O
Diaoyutai,	O
2	O
South	O
Street	O
Fucheng	O
Road,	O
Haidian	O
District	O
Beijing,	O
PRC	O

6/F,	O
NCI	O
Tower	O
A12	O
Jianguomenwai	O
Avenue	O
Chaoyang	O
District,	O
Beijing	O
China	O
as	O
to	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
law:	O

As	O
to	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
law:	O
Conyers	B-ORG
Dill	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Pearman	E-ORG
P.O.	O
Box	O
2681	O
Grand	O
KY1-1111	O

Liu	B-PERSON
Jing	E-PERSON
(劉景)	O
Room	O
1205,	O
Block	O
6	O
Lugu	O
Xiaozhen	O
Yuelu	O
District,	O
Changsha	O
Hunan	O
PRC	O

Legal	B-TITLE
Advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
our	I-TITLE
Company	E-TITLE
As	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
law:	O
Loong	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Yeung	E-ORG
Room	O
1603,	O
16th	O
Floor	O
China	O
Building	O
29	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Central,	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Lam	I-PERSON
Yuk	I-PERSON
Ling	E-PERSON
(林玉玲)	O
(ACS,	O
ACIS)	O
31/F,	O
Tower	O
Two	O
Times	O
Square	O
1	O
Matheson	O
Street,	O
Causeway	O
Bay	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Barrister-at-law	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Chambers	O
38th	O
Floor	O
Gloucester	O
Tower	O
The	O
Landmark	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
VBG	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Dr.	B-PERSON
FRANK	I-PERSON
NINGJUN	I-PERSON
JIANG	E-PERSON
4288	O
Long	O
Dong	O
Ave.	O
#221	O
Pudong	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Tax	B-TITLE
adviser	E-TITLE
PricewaterhouseCoopers	B-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
21/F	O
Edinburgh	O
Tower	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

SPDB	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
33/F,	O
SPD	O
Bank	O
Tower	O
One	O
Hennessy	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Nomination	O
committee	O
Wu	O
Daxiang	O
(吳大香)	O
(Chairman)	O

52	O
China	B-ORG
Everbright	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

First	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
4512,	O
45/F	O
The	O
Center	O
99	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
TAN	I-PERSON
Henry,	E-PERSON
BBS.,	O
JP	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Or	I-PERSON
Kevin	E-PERSON
(柯衍峰)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
26/F,	O
Tower	O
8	O
The	O
Wings	O
No.	O
9	O
Tong	O
Yin	O
Street	O
Tseung	O
Kwan	O
O	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Level	O
39	O
Two	O
International	O
Finance	O
Centre	O
8	O
Street	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
as	O
to	O
PRC	O
laws:	O

Members	B-TITLE
of	I-TITLE
audit	I-TITLE
committee	E-TITLE
Ms.	B-PERSON
Lee	I-PERSON
Wing	I-PERSON
Yin	I-PERSON
Jessica	E-PERSON
(Chairman)	O

Legal	B-TITLE
adviser	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor,	I-TITLE
Joint	I-TITLE
Bookrunners,	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	I-TITLE

Mr.	B-PERSON
Leung	I-PERSON
Ka	I-PERSON
Tin	E-PERSON
(梁家鈿先生)	O
Flat	O
F,	O
18th	O
Floor	O
Block	O
9,	O
Le	O
Point	O
8	O
King	O
Leng	O
Road	O
Tiu	O
Keng	O
Tseung	O
Kwan	O
O	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Yu	I-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
Leung(余國良)	E-PERSON
Flat	O
G,	O
22nd	O
Floor,	O
Block	O
6	O
Sorrento	O
1	O
Austin	O
Road	O
West	O
Kowloon,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O


Registered	O
Public	O
Interest	O
Entity	O
Auditor	O
22/F,	O
Prince's	O
Building	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Solicitor	O
of	O
HKSAR	O
Flat	O
G,	O
28/F,	O
Block	O
10	O
Nan	O
Fung	O
Sun	O
Chuen	O
19	O
Greig	O
Crescent	O
Quarry	O
Bay	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
China	B-ORG
Tonghai	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
permitted	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
2	O
future	O
contracts),	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
6	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
and	O
9	O
(asset	O
management)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
18/F–19/F,	O
Building	O
29	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Zhang	I-PERSON
Hailin	E-PERSON
(張海林)	O
Room	O
2210,	O
Building	O
9	O
Fangzhouyuan	O
Xiaoqu	O
Beisihuandong	O
Jia	O
Road	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
Beijing	O
PRC	O

Emperio	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
And	I-ORG
Assets	I-ORG
Management	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Internal	B-TITLE
control	I-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE
RSM	B-ORG
Consulting	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
29th	O
Floor,	O
Lee	O
Garden	O
Two	O
28	O
Yun	O
Ping	O
Road	O
Causeway	O
Bay	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Cheng	I-PERSON
Chun	I-PERSON
Shing	E-PERSON
(鄭鎮昇)	O
(chairman)	O

Hong	O
Kong	O
Underwriter(s)	E-TITLE
Head	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Shoulders	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
conduct	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lam	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON
Yuen	E-PERSON
(林志遠先生)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
5/F,	O
Block	O
5	O
Grand	O
Palisades	O
8	O
Shan	O
Yin	O
Road	O
Tai	O
Po,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lai	I-PERSON
Chun	I-PERSON
Yu	E-PERSON
(黎振宇)	O
G/F	O
12	O
Hoi	O
Pa	O
Village	O
North-East	O
Terrace	O
Tsuen	O
Wan	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

PO	O
Box	O
309	O
Ugland	O
House,	O
Grand	O
Cayman	O
KY1-1104	O
Islands	O

Jianfa	B-PERSON
Lai	E-PERSON
賴建法	O
Tianjing	O
Group	O
3,	O
Gewu	O
Village	O
Zhongshan	O
Country,	O
Tonglu	O
County	O
Zhejiang	O
Province,	O
China	O

40th	O
Floor,	O
Office	O
Tower	O
A	O
Beijing	O
Fortune	O
Plaza	O
7	O
Dongsanhuan	O
Zhonglu	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
PRC	O
as	O
to	O
Indonesian	O
law:	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
LI	I-PERSON
Quan	E-PERSON
(李泉)	O
.	O
Room	O
601,	O
Unit	O
1	O
Building	O
10,	O
Yangguangshangdong	O
Chaoyang	O
District,	O
Beijing	O
the	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ng	I-PERSON
Tian	I-PERSON
Fah	E-PERSON

Sole	B-TITLE
Sponsor	E-TITLE
Ample	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

As	O
to	O
Cambodia	O
law	O
Heng	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Partners	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Group	E-ORG
Unit	O
249	O
1st	O
Floor,	O
Oriental	O
Tower	O
by	O
Meridian	O
Harvard	O
Street,	O
Koh	O
Pich	O
Phnom	O
Penh	O

Withers	B-ORG
LLP	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ting	I-PERSON
Yuk	I-PERSON
Anthony	I-PERSON
Wu	E-PERSON
(胡定旭)	O
Room	O
4330	O
Four	O
Seasons	O
Place	O
8	O
Finance	O
Street	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Walkers	B-ORG
Corporate	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
27	O
Hospital	O
Road,	O
George	O
Town	O
Grand	O
Cayman,	O
KY1-9008	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O

Company	B-TITLE
secretary	E-TITLE

Ms.	B-PERSON
Siu	I-PERSON
Pui	I-PERSON
Wah	E-PERSON
14/F.,	O
Golden	O
Centre	O
188	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joincap	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
conduct	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Remuneration	B-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Xiao	I-PERSON
Huan	I-PERSON
Wei	E-PERSON
(肖煥偉)	O
(chairman)	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinators	E-TITLE
Elstone	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
FAN	I-PERSON
Shuyang	E-PERSON
(樊舒暘)	O
.	O
Room	O
2,	O
No.1	O
Lane	O
9,	O
Fenyang	O
Road	O
Xuhui	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Guotai	B-ORG
Junan	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
regulated	O
activities	O

Registered	O
office	O
in	O
the	O
Cayman	O
Island	O
Cricket	O
Square	O
Hutchins	O
Drive	O
P.O.	O
Box	O
2681	O
Grand	O
Cayman,	O
KY1-1111	O
Islands	O

Leung	B-PERSON
Ka	I-PERSON
Sing	E-PERSON
(梁嘉聲)	O
Flat	O
B,	O
2/F	O
Shung	O
King	O
Mansion	O
114	O
Boundary	O
Street	O
Ho	O
Man	O
Tin,	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chen	E-PERSON
Bingqiang(陳炳强)	O
(Mr.	O
Ernest	O
Chen)	O
Room	O
2102,	O
Block	O
C,	O
Tower	O
3	O
Shui	O
Yue	O
Cheng	O
Bang	O
Xinrong	O
Lu	O
Daliang	O
Area,	O
Shunde	O
District	O
Foshan	O
City,	O
Guangdong	O
PRC	O
Bingqiang	O

24	O
Peck	O
Seah	O
Street	O
#02-03	O
Nehsons	O
Building	O
Singapore	O
079314	O
Receiving	O
Bank	O
.	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lee	I-PERSON
Yiu	I-PERSON
Ming	E-PERSON
(李耀明)	O
(HKICPA)	O

Company	O
Secretary	O
Mr.	O
Tsoi	O
Ka	O
Shing(蔡嘉誠)(HKICPA)	O
1st	O
Floor,	O
51	O
Sheung	O
Wo	O
Che	O
Shatin,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Conrad	B-ORG
Investment	I-ORG
Services	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities),	O
2	O
futures	O
contracts)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
securities)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
23/F,	O
Tung	O
Hip	O
Commercial	O
Building	O
244–248	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central,	O
Sheung	O
Wan	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chong	I-PERSON
Man	I-PERSON
Hung	I-PERSON
Jeffrey	E-PERSON
(Chairman)	O

As	O
to	O
Cayman	O
Islands	O
law:	O
Conyers	B-ORG
Dill	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Pearman	E-ORG

Li	B-PERSON
Haijun	E-PERSON
(李海軍)	O
Room	O
13A05,	O
Building	O
5	O
Golden	O
International,	O
Dongmen	O
Town	O
Luocheng	O
Mulao	O
Autonomous	O
County	O
Guangxi,	O
China	O

Haitong	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

UOB	B-ORG
Kay	I-ORG
Hian	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Limited,	E-ORG
or	O
UOBKH	B-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Nomination	O
committee	O
Mr.	O
Chew	O
Keat	O
Yeow	O
(Chairman)	O
Chan	O
Ka	O
Yu	O
Lee	O
Yan	O
Fai	O
Lim	O
Fung	O
Chor	O

156	O
Our	B-TITLE
Legal	I-TITLE
Advisers	E-TITLE

Mr.	B-PERSON
Auyang	I-PERSON
Pak	I-PERSON
Hong	I-PERSON
Bernard	E-PERSON
(歐陽伯康)	O
(Chairman)	O

Professor	B-PERSON
Ho	I-PERSON
Richard	I-PERSON
Yan	I-PERSON
Ki	E-PERSON
(何炘基教授)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
6/F.,	O
Tower	O
15	O
Providence	O
Peak	O
8	O
Fo	O
Chun	O
Road,	O
Tai	O
Po	O
New	O
Territories,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Independent	B-TITLE
Property	I-TITLE
Valuer	E-TITLE
D&P	B-ORG
China	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lam	I-PERSON
Sai	I-PERSON
Yu	I-PERSON
Geoffrey	E-PERSON
(林世愉)	O
House	O
2	O
63	O
Deep	O
Water	O
Bay	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Sponsor	E-TITLE
Guosen	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Co.,	I-ORG
Ltd.	E-ORG

Joint	B-TITLE
Representatives	E-TITLE
China	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
Hong	I-ORG
Kong	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Co-lead	B-TITLE
Manager	E-TITLE
I	B-ORG
Win	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Carlyon	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
E	O
22/F	O
Tower	O
A	O
Billion	O
Centre	O
1	O
Wang	O
Kwong	O
Road	O
Kowloon	O
Bay	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Principal	O
place	O
of	O
business	O
in	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
31/F.,	O
148	O
Electric	O
Road	O
North	O
Point,	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	E-TITLE
Elstone	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Flat	O
C,	O
5/F	O
La	O
Salle	O
House	O
11A–11C	O
Road	O
Kowloon	O
Tong	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Chinese	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Li	I-PERSON
Xue	E-PERSON
(李雪先生)	O
Room	O
601	O
Unit	O
2,	O
Building	O
5	O
23	O
Xianggang	O
East	O
Road	O
Qingdao,	O
PRC	O

Allen	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Gledhill	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG
One	O
Marina	O
Boulevard	O
#28-00	O
Singapore	O
018989	O
As	O
to	O
Bermuda	O
law	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Shuk	I-PERSON
Fong	E-PERSON
30K,	O
The	O
Masterpiece	O
18	O
Hanoi	O
Road	O
Tsim	O
Sha	O
Tsui	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Industry	B-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE
Frost	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Sullivan	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
1706	O
One	O
Exchange	O
Square	O
8	O
Connaught	O
Place	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

CHOW	B-PERSON
Kyan	I-PERSON
Mervyn	E-PERSON
(周紀恩)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
13/F	O
8	O
Shiu	O
Fai	O
Terrace	O
Mid	O
Level	O
East	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Chen	B-PERSON
Danxia	E-PERSON
(陳丹霞)	O
No.	O
29,	O
Huayuan	O
1	O
Street	O
Yuexiu	O
District	O
Guangzhou,	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
China	O

Allbright	B-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Offices	I-ORG
(Shenzhen)	E-ORG

Guotai	B-ORG
Junan	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
27/F.,	O
Low	O
Block,	O
Grand	O
Millennium	O
Plaza	O
181	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Sole	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinator,	I-TITLE
Bookrunner	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Manager	I-TITLE

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Cheong	I-PERSON
Tat	E-PERSON
(陳昌達)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
7/F	O
Block	O
3,	O
City	O
Garden	O
233	O
Electric	O
Road	O
North	O
Point,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Werner	I-PERSON
Peter	I-PERSON
VAN	I-PERSON
ECK	I-PERSON
Kwok	I-PERSON
King	I-PERSON
Kingsley	E-PERSON

Sinomax	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
2705-6,	O
27/F	O
Tower	O
One,	O
Lippo	O
Centre	O
89	O
Queensway	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

As	O
to	O
U.S.	O
law:	O
DLA	B-ORG
Piper	I-ORG
Middle	I-ORG
East	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG
PO	O
Box	O
121662	O
Level	O
9,	O
Standard	O
Chartered	O
Tower	O
Downtown	O
Dubai	O
The	O
United	O
Arab	O
Emirates	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Kam	I-PERSON
Leung	E-PERSON
(陳錦良)	O
Flat	O
D,	O
10th	O
Floor,	O
Block	O
9	O
Dawning	O
Views	O
23	O
Yat	O
Ming	O
Road	O
Fanling,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
PEI	I-PERSON
Dapeng	E-PERSON
(裴大鵬)	O
.	O
Room	O
401,	O
No.	O
20	O
Lane	O
500,	O
Xianxia	O
West	O
Road	O
Changning	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
ZHU	E-PERSON
Jianqin(朱建琴女士)	O
Villa	O
no.	O
22,	O
Sunny	O
Garden,	O
Wenshan	O
West	O
Road,	O
Hangzhou	O
City,	O
Zhejiang	O
Province,	O
PRC	O
Jianqin	O

Company	B-TITLE
secretary	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Tsang	I-PERSON
Kai	I-PERSON
Ming	E-PERSON
Certified	O
Public	O
Accountant	O
Flat	O
D,	O
18/F	O
Tower	O
7A,	O
Oceanaire	O
18	O
Po	O
Tai	O
Street	O
Ma	O
On	O
Shan	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Southwest	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HK)	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
by	O
the	O
SFC	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
SFO	O

Compliance	B-TITLE
adviser	E-TITLE
Red	B-ORG
Sun	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Room	O
3303,	O
33rd	O
Floor,	O
West	O
Tower	O
Shun	O
Tak	O
Centre	O
168–200	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
engaged	O
in	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Property	B-TITLE
valuer	E-TITLE
Colliers	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Suite	O
5701	O
Central	O
Plaza	O
18	O
Harbour	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Xingyao	B-PERSON
Chen	E-PERSON
(陳興垚)	O
No.	O
2,	O
Unit	O
3,	O
52/F	O
Huanshan	O
Village	O
Beijing	O
People's	O
Republic	O
of	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
TIAN	E-PERSON
Jingyan(田景岩先生)	O
No.	O
603,	O
Gate	O
3,	O
6/F,	O
Jiaolin,	O
Hepingli,	O
Dongcheng	O
District,	O
Beijing	O
City,	O
PRC	O
Chinese	O
Jingyan	O

Ample	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
A,	O
14/F.	O
Two	O
Chinachem	O
Plaza	O
135	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

15/F,	O
Shanghai	O
Commercial	O
Bank	O
Tower	O
12	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
uSmart	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wu	I-PERSON
Tak	I-PERSON
Lung	E-PERSON
(吳德龍)	O
Flat	O
C,	O
11/F,	O
Tower	O
11	O
Pacific	O
Palisades	O
1	O
Braemar	O
Hill	O
Road,	O
North	O
Point	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Hong	I-TITLE
Kong	I-TITLE
Underwriters	E-TITLE
Haitong	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O
for	O
purpose	O
of	O
SFO)	O

Qi	B-PERSON
Xiangzhong	E-PERSON
(亓向中)	O
No.	O
2	O
Villa	O
Yujing	O
Mingcheng	O
Pedestrian	O
Street	O
East	O
Suiping	O
County	O
Henan	O
Province	O
PRC	O

YAO	B-PERSON
Yaping	E-PERSON
(姚亞平)	O
Room	O
602,	O
Unit	O
5	O
No.	O
6	O
Huishengyuan	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
Beijing,	O
PRC	O

Watson	B-ORG
Farley	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Williams	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG

As	O
to	O
Malaysia	O
laws	O
Chooi	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
+	I-ORG
Cheang	I-ORG
Ariff	E-ORG
Advocates	O
Solicitors,	O
CCA	O
@	O
Bangsar	O
Level	O
5,	O
Menara	O
BRDB	O
285,	O
Jalan	O
Maarof	O
Bukit	O
Bandaraya	O
59000	O
Kuala	O
Lumpur	O

Alameda	O
Dr.	O
Carlos	O
d'Assumpçáo	O
No.	O
249	O
Edif.	O
China	O
Civil	O
Plaza	O
7	O
Andar	O
E&F	O
Macau	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Jia	I-PERSON
Xiaogang	I-PERSON
Wu	I-PERSON
Yong	E-PERSON

Ms.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Nga	I-PERSON
Chun	E-PERSON
Flat	O
F,	O
41/F	O
Tower	O
2B,	O
The	O
Pavilia	O
Bay	O
51	O
Wing	O
Shun	O
Street	O
Tsuen	O
Wan,	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Industry	B-TITLE
consultant	E-TITLE
Frost	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Sullivan	I-ORG
(Beijing)	I-ORG
Inc.	I-ORG
Shanghai	I-ORG
Branch	I-ORG
Co.	E-ORG
1018,	O
Tower	O
B	O
500	O
Yunjin	O
Road	O
China	O

Dr.	B-PERSON
Wong	I-PERSON
Tin	I-PERSON
Yau	I-PERSON
Kelvin	E-PERSON
(黃天祐)	O
.	O
Room	O
2,	O
4/F	O
Block	O
D	O
Greenville	O
Gardens	O
Shiu	O
Fai	O
Terrace	O
No.	O
14-17	O
Stubbs	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Harmonia	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Hills	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Co.	E-ORG

Chinese	B-PERSON
Mr.	I-PERSON
Hou	I-PERSON
Zukuan	E-PERSON
(侯祖寬)	O
Room	O
1906,	O
Jinyuan	O
Building	O
Jiangwan	O
Road	O
Lingxi	O
Town	O
Cangnan	O
County	O
Zhejiang	O
Province	O
PRC	O

As	O
to	O
Singapore	O
law	O
Bird	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
ATMD	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG
2	O
Shenton	O
Way	O
#18-01	O
SGX	O
Centre	O
1	O
068804	O
Republic	O
of	O

Tan	B-PERSON
Michael	I-PERSON
Zhen	I-PERSON
Shan	E-PERSON
(譚鎮山)	O
Flat	O
F,	O
5/F,	O
Oak	O
Mansion	O
Taikoo	O
Shing	O
20	O
Tai	O
Koo	O
Wan	O
Road	O
Quarry	O
Bay	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(香港太古灣島道20號太古城	O
紫樺閣5字樓F室)	O

Sponsor	S-TITLE
Grande	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
engaging	O
in	O
type	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activity	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Room	O
1301,	O
13/F	O
Tung	O
Wai	O
Commercial	O
Building	O
109-111	O
Gloucester	O
Road	O
Wan	O
Chai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
for	O
carrying	O
on	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO)	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Chan	I-PERSON
Tim	I-PERSON
Yiu	I-PERSON
Raymond	E-PERSON
(陳添耀)	O
Flat	O
C,	O
1/F	O
No.	O
70	O
Sing	O
Woo	O
Road	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Cao	I-PERSON
Guohua	E-PERSON
(曹國華)	O
No.	O
11,	O
Baishulin	O
Shapingba	O
District	O
Chongqing,	O
PRC	O

Co-Managers	S-TITLE
Marketsense	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
7801–03,	O
The	O
Center	O
99	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
A	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
Type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
4	O
(advising	O
on	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Receiving	B-TITLE
Banks	E-TITLE
.	O

Co-lead	B-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE

Joint	B-TITLE
Bookrunners	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Sun	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
2412–13,	O
24/F	O
China	O
Merchants	O
Tower	O
Shun	O
Tak	O
Centre	O
168–200	O
Connaught	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

HGNH	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Co.,	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Compliance	B-TITLE
Adviser	E-TITLE
Celestial	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
TUNG	I-PERSON
Fong	I-PERSON
Ngai	E-PERSON
(董貺漄)	O
House	O
2,	O
Carmel	O
Avenue	O
Royal	O
Palms,	O
Phase	O
A	O
Yuen	O
Long	O
New	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Kong	I-PERSON
Jiannan	E-PERSON
(孔健楠)	O
Flat	O
A,	O
37/F,	O
Block	O
T5	O
Bel-Air	O
on	O
the	O
Peak	O
68	O
Avenue	O
Cyber	O
Port	O
Hong	O

Maples	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Calder	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
LLP	E-ORG
53rd	O
Floor,	O
The	O
Center	O
99	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Legal	B-TITLE
Advisers	I-TITLE
to	I-TITLE
the	I-TITLE
Sole	I-TITLE
Sponsor	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Underwriters	E-TITLE
.	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinators	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
Huajin	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(International)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Ms.	B-PERSON
Chu	I-PERSON
Wing	I-PERSON
Yin	E-PERSON
Certified	O
Public	O
Accountant	O

Beijing	B-ORG
DeHeng	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Offices	E-ORG

NGAN	B-PERSON
Edith	I-PERSON
Manling	E-PERSON
(顏文玲)	O
Wu	O
Yee	O
Sun	O
College	O
Master's	O
Lodge	O
Chinese	O
University	O
of	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Shatin,	O

Units	O
4101-04,	O
41st	O
Floor	O
Sun	O
Hung	O
Kai	O
Centre	O
30	O
Harbour	O
Road	O
Wanchai	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(Solicitors	O
of	O
SAR)	O

68/F,	O
Cheung	O
Kong	O
Center	O
2	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
J.P.	B-ORG
Morgan	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(Asia	I-ORG
Pacific)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Public	O
Offering	O
only)	O
28/F,	O
Chater	O
House	O
8	O
Connaught	O
25	O
Bank	O
Street	O
Canary	O
Wharf	O
London	O
E14	O
5JP	O
United	O
Kingdom	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wu	I-PERSON
Ye	E-PERSON
(吳曄)	O
Room	O
1103,	O
Building	O
15	O
District	O
1,	O
Wanfang	O
Yuan	O
Fengtai	O
District,	O
Beijing,	O
China	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Xu	I-PERSON
Rongnian	E-PERSON
(許榮年)	O
Room	O
201,	O
Unit	O
1,	O
Building	O
22	O
Hanlin	O
Garden,	O
Shangcheng	O
District	O
Hangzhou	O
Zhejiang	O
province	O
PRC	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
YIP	I-PERSON
Kwong	I-PERSON
Cheung	E-PERSON
(葉廣祥)	O
Flat	O
7,	O
14/F	O
Block	O
A	O
New	O
Town	O
Mansion	O
Tuen	O
Mun	O
Territories	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Suite	O
3509,	O
35/F	O
Tower	O
2,	O
Lippo	O
Centre	O
89	O
Queensway	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
(a	O
licensed	O
corporation	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
2	O
future	O
contracts)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
SFO)	O

Compliance	B-TITLE
Advisor	E-TITLE
Huatai	B-ORG
Financial	I-ORG
Holdings	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
LI	I-PERSON
Yifan	E-PERSON
(李軼梵)	O
1	O
Jumen	O
Road	O
Apartment	O
1-2804	O
Shanghai,	O
PRC	O
U.S.	O

Realord	B-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Pacific	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Suite	O
2402,	O
24/F	O
Jardine	O
House	O
1	O
Connaught	O
Place	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Ou	I-PERSON
Xiaojie	E-PERSON
(歐小傑)	O
1-2-101	O
Shiqiao	O
International	O
Trade	O
Apartment	O
No.	O
16	O
East	O
Third	O
Ring	O
Middle	O
Road	O
Chaoyang	O
District	O
Beijing,	O
China	O

Sriram	B-PERSON
CHANDRASEKAR	E-PERSON
40	O
Keppel	O
Bay	O
Drive	O
#05-98	O
Singapore	O
098655	O
Indian	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wu	I-PERSON
Tak	I-PERSON
Lung	E-PERSON
(吳德龍)	O
(Chairman)	O

Citigroup	B-ORG
Global	I-ORG
Markets	I-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
(in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Hong	O
Kong	O
Public	O
Offering	O
only)	O
50th	O
Floor,	O
Champion	O
Tower	O
3	O
Garden	O
Road,	O
Central	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Yu	I-PERSON
Gao	E-PERSON
(高煜)	O
Apt.	O
9-901	O
873	O
Xiangyin	O
Road	O
Shanghai	O
200433	O
PRC	O

Fulbright	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
33/F	O
Cosco	O
Tower,	O
Grand	O
Millennium	O
Plaza	O
183	O
Queen's	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Livermore	B-ORG
Holdings	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
Unit	O
1214A,	O
12/F,	O
Tower	O
II	O
Cheung	O
Sha	O
Wan	O
Plaza	O
833	O
Road	O
Kowloon	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Kao	I-PERSON
Yi-Ping	E-PERSON
(高亦平)	O
12/F,	O
No.	O
83	O
Section	O
4,	O
Chengde	O
Road	O
Shilin	O
District,	O
Taipei	O
City	O
Taiwan	O

Industry	B-TITLE
Consultant	E-TITLE
.	O
Frost	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Sullivan	I-ORG
(Beijing)	I-ORG
Inc.,	I-ORG
Shanghai	I-ORG
Branch	I-ORG
Co.	E-ORG
Room	O
1018,	O
Tower	O
B,	O
Greenland	O
Hui	O
Centre,	O
No.	O
500	O
Yunjin	O
Road,	O
Xuhui	O
District,	O
Shanghai,	O
PRC	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Global	I-TITLE
Coordinators	E-TITLE
Cinda	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
A	O
corporation	O
licensed	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
type	O
1	O
(dealing	O
in	O
securities)	O
and	O
6	O
(advising	O
on	O
corporate	O
finance)	O
regulated	O
activities	O
under	O
the	O
SFO	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Lim	I-PERSON
Yu	I-PERSON
Neng	I-PERSON
Paul	E-PERSON
(林御能)	O
134	O
Holland	O
Grove	O
View	O
Singapore	O
276284	O
Singaporean	O

Global	B-ORG
Group	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

First	B-ORG
Shanghai	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Ltd.	E-ORG
19/F.,	O
Wing	O
On	O
House	O
71	O
Des	O
Voeux	O
Road	O
Central	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Liu	I-PERSON
Tongyou	E-PERSON
(劉同友)	O
Flat	O
2305,	O
Block	O
3	O
80,	O
Dapu	O
Road	O
Huangpu	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O

Ms.	B-PERSON
LI	I-PERSON
Xiaoling	E-PERSON
(李曉玲)	O
Room	O
606,	O
Unit	O
3,	O
Building	O
C1-5,	O
Baoli	O
Luolan	O
Xianggu	O
Community,	O
High-tech	O
Industrial	O
Development	O
Zone,	O
Changchun	O
City,	O
Jilin	O
Province,	O
PRC	O

Audit	B-TITLE
Committee	E-TITLE
Mr.	B-PERSON
Ho	I-PERSON
Ka	E-PERSON
Chun(何家進)(Chairman)	O
Yu	I-PERSON
Kwok	E-PERSON
Leung(余國良)	O
Liang	E-PERSON
Chi(梁赤)	O
Chun	I-PERSON
Leung	I-PERSON
Chi	I-PERSON

Han	B-ORG
Kun	I-ORG
Law	I-ORG
Offices	E-ORG
Room	O
03-04,	O
21/F,	O
Kerry	O
Plaza	O
Tower	O
3	O
1-1	O
Zhongxinsi	O
Road	O
Futian	O
District	O
Shenzhen,	O
Guangdong	O
PRC	O

Reporting	B-TITLE
Accountants	I-TITLE
and	I-TITLE
Auditor	E-TITLE
BDO	B-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Joint	B-TITLE
Lead	I-TITLE
Managers	E-TITLE
CMBC	B-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
45/F,	O
One	O
Exchange	O
Square	O
8	O
Connaught	O
Place	O
Central,	O
Hong	O
Kong	O

Mr.	B-PERSON
Wang	I-PERSON
Yinhu	E-PERSON
(王銀虎)	O
Room	O
3A,	O
Building	O
11	O
Lanxi	O
Valley	O
I	O
Yanshan	O
Road	O
Nanshan	O
District,	O
Shenzhen	O
Guangdong	O
Province	O
PRC	O

Alpha	B-ORG
International	I-ORG
Securities	I-ORG
(HONG	I-ORG
KONG)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Industry	B-TITLE
Consultant	E-TITLE
.	O
China	B-ORG
Insights	I-ORG
Consultancy	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG
10/F,	O
Tomorrow	O
Square	O
399	O
West	O
Nanjing	O
Road	O
Huangpu	O
District	O
Shanghai	O

Compliance	B-TITLE
adviser	E-TITLE
Orient	B-ORG
Capital	I-ORG
(Hong	I-ORG
Kong)	I-ORG
Limited	E-ORG

Mr.	B-PERSON
WANG	I-PERSON
Yuguo	E-PERSON
(王玉國)	O
Room	O
1408,	O
Building	O
3,	O
Changying	O
Shiji	O
Village,	O
Chaoyang	O
District,	O
Changchun	O
City,	O
Jilin	O
Province,	O
PRC	O

Joint	B-TITLE
Company	I-TITLE
Secretaries	E-TITLE
.	O
Mr.	B-PERSON
Fan	I-PERSON
Shuyang	E-PERSON
Room	O
2	O
No.1,	O
Lane	O
9	O
Fen	O
Yang	O
Road	O
Xuhui	O
District	O
Shanghai	O
PRC	O
